{"publish_date":"December 31, 2009","entities":[["Michelle Kwan","PER"],["Korea","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["Michelle","PER"],["Seoul","LOC"],["Pyeong","ORG"],["##chang","LOC"],["Go","PER"],["##yang","PER"],["Olympics","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Forces Korea","ORG"],["Yong","LOC"],["##san Military Garrison","ORG"],["Dar","PER"],["##lene Kirk","PER"],["Brian Gibel","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Embassy Seoul","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 31, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["N","PER"],["##est","PER"],["##or Tedesco","PER"],["Argentine","MISC"],["Fu","MISC"],["##l","MISC"],["##bright","MISC"],["Student","MISC"],["Ted","PER"],["##es","PER"],["##co","PER"],["Argentine","MISC"],["##an","MISC"],["Argentine","MISC"],["##ans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Ted","PER"],["##es","PER"],["##co","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Boston","LOC"],["Fu","MISC"],["##l","MISC"],["##bright Program","MISC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Buenos Aires Colon Theater","LOC"],["National Art Institute University","ORG"],["Ted","PER"],["##es","PER"],["##co","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Z","ORG"],["##ona","ORG"],["##s de Accion Prioritaria z","MISC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Ted","ORG"],["##es","ORG"],["##co","ORG"],["Ted","PER"],["##es","PER"],["##co","PER"],["Argentina","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Ted","PER"],["##es","PER"],["##co","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[". Embassy","LOC"],["Villa 31","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Joshua Bell Tedesco","PER"],["Fu","MISC"],["Ted","ORG"],["##es","PER"],["##co","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 30, 2009","entities":[["Burma","LOC"],["British","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"],["Burma","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Burma","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Burmese","MISC"],["Burmese","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 29, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Republic of Haiti","LOC"],["Haiti","LOC"],["To","PER"],["##uss","PER"],["##ain","PER"],["##t Louverture Jean Jacques Dessalines","PER"],["Alexandre Petion","PER"],["Haitian Americans","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Haiti","LOC"],["Haitian","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Haiti","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 29, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Chad","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Chad","MISC"],["##ian","MISC"],["Mo","PER"],["##uss","PER"],["##a Faki","PER"],["Sudan","MISC"],["##ese","MISC"],["G","PER"],["##ha","PER"],["##zi Salahuddin","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["##s of","ORG"],["Chad","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["N","LOC"],["'","LOC"],["D","LOC"],["##ja","LOC"],["##men","LOC"],["##a Chad","LOC"],["Dar","MISC"],["##fu","MISC"],["##r Peace Process The","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["Chad","LOC"],["su","MISC"],["##dan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 28, 2009","entities":[["Ian","PER"],["Embassy","ORG"],["##EL","PER"],["The","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Embassy","ORG"],["London","LOC"],["London","LOC"],["Embassy","LOC"],["Nigeria","LOC"],["Abu","LOC"],["##ja","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["London","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["##Y","PER"],["##Y","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 27, 2009","entities":[["Royal Thai Government","ORG"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Office of the United Nations","ORG"],["Royal Thai Government","ORG"],["Laos","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Lao People ' s Democratic Republic","LOC"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Hu","LOC"],["##ay Nam Khao Camp","LOC"],["Pet","LOC"],["##cha","LOC"],["##bu","LOC"],["##n","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["Royal Thai Government","ORG"],["##hao","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["H","MISC"],["##mon","MISC"],["##g","MISC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Non","LOC"],["##g Khai","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["Office of the","ORG"],["Thailand","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Eric Schwartz","PER"],["Population Refugees","ORG"],["Migration","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["##s of","ORG"],["Thailand","LOC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Royal Thai Government","ORG"],["Royal Thai Government","ORG"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 24, 2009","entities":[["Sean Goldman","PER"],["David Goldman","PER"],["Rio de Janeiro","LOC"],["New Jersey","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Hague Convention on International Child Abduction","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Chinese","MISC"],["Liu Xiaobo","PER"],["Liu","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Embassy","ORG"],["Covenant on Civil and Political Rights","MISC"],["China","LOC"],["Liu","PER"],["Chinese","MISC"],["Government of China","ORG"],["Chinese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Iranian","MISC"],["Amir Hossein Ardebili","PER"],["The","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Tan","PER"],["##d","PER"],["##ja","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Government of Niger","ORG"],["Government of Niger","ORG"],["Niger","LOC"],["Niger","LOC"],["Niger","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Richard M. Nixon","PER"],["Gerald R. Ford","PER"],["Richard Nixon","PER"],["Brett","MISC"],["##on Woods","MISC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Smithsonian Agreement","MISC"],["Group of Seven G - 7","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["White House","LOC"],["Trade Act","MISC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["jack","PER"],["##son","PER"],["M","LOC"],["##F","LOC"],["##N","LOC"],["Soviet Union","LOC"],["Jewish","MISC"],["Tokyo Round of","MISC"],["General Agreement on Tariffs","MISC"],["Nixon","PER"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Brazil","LOC"],["Embassy","LOC"],["Brasil","LOC"],["##ia","LOC"],["Rio de Janeiro","LOC"],["Goldman","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Sean Goldman","PER"],["David","PER"],["Kingston Jamaica","LOC"],["Embassy","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Op","ORG"],["Center","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["National Assembly","ORG"],["Southern Sudan","LOC"],["NC","ORG"],["##P","ORG"],["NC","ORG"],["##P","ORG"],["SP","ORG"],["##LM","ORG"],["A","MISC"],["##by","MISC"],["##ei","MISC"],["Southern Sudan","LOC"],["The United States","LOC"],["National Security Act","MISC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 21, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Ma","PER"],["##ks","PER"],["##hari","PER"],["##p Aushev","PER"],["Na","LOC"],["##z","LOC"],["##ran Ingushetia","LOC"],["The State Department","ORG"],["Au","PER"],["##she","PER"],["##v","PER"],["Russia","LOC"],["North Caucasus","LOC"],["Au","PER"],["##she","PER"],["##v","PER"],["Russian","MISC"],["Government","ORG"],["North Caucasus","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 19, 2009","entities":[["Royal Government of Cambodia","ORG"],["China","LOC"],["U","MISC"],["##igh","MISC"],["##ur","MISC"],["China","LOC"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Cambodian","MISC"],["Office of the UN","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["China","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Government of Iran","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN Third Committee","ORG"],["Iranian","MISC"],["Government of Iran","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN Special Rapporteur","ORG"],["Special Rapport","ORG"],["##eur","MISC"],["Special Rapporteur","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Romania","LOC"],["Central Europe","LOC"],["Tim","LOC"],["##is","LOC"],["##oar","LOC"],["##a","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"],["Romanian","MISC"],["European Union","ORG"],["NATO The United States","ORG"],["Romania","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Department","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Di","ORG"],["##p","ORG"],["##N","ORG"],["##ote","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Di","PER"],["##p","PER"],["##N","PER"],["##ote","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Di","ORG"],["##p","ORG"],["##N","ORG"],["##ote","ORG"],["Di","ORG"],["##p","ORG"],["##N","ORG"],["##ote","ORG"],["Sudan Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Global Women ' s","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Richard Nixon","PER"],["Gerald Ford","PER"],["Nixon","PER"],["Nixon","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Antarctic","MISC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Antarctic","MISC"],["Nixon Ford","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Morocco","LOC"],["Am","PER"],["##ina","PER"],["##to","PER"],["##u Haidar","PER"],["Robert F. Kennedy","PER"],["Spain","LOC"],["Moroccan","MISC"],["Western Sahara","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Ban Ki Moon","PER"],["UN","MISC"],["sponsored","MISC"],["Man","MISC"],["##has","MISC"],["##set","MISC"],["Christopher Ross","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Copenhagen","LOC"],["Todd Stern","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["o","PER"],["##ba","PER"],["##ma","PER"],["Todd Stern","PER"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["Recovery Act","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Major Economies Forum on Energy and Climate","ORG"],["G","MISC"],["##20","MISC"],["Asian Pacific Economic Cooperation","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Horn of Africa","LOC"],["Somali","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["International Maritime Organization","ORG"],["United Nations Office on Drugs and Crime","ORG"],["Contact Group on","ORG"],["Pi","MISC"],["##racy","ORG"],["the Coast of Somalia","LOC"],["Somalia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Ministry of External Relations of Brazil","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Ministry of External Relations of Brazil","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["Brasil","LOC"],["##ia","LOC"],["Washington D. C.","LOC"],["Brasil","LOC"],["##ia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["-","MISC"],["Brazil","MISC"],["United States","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["Brazil","MISC"],["Joint","MISC"],["Commission","ORG"],["J","ORG"],["##CM","MISC"],["on Science and Technology","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["J","MISC"],["##CM","MISC"],["American Council on Competitiveness","ORG"],["Consul","ORG"],["##tative","ORG"],["Committee on Agriculture","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["CC","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["UN","ORG"],["FA","ORG"],["##O","ORG"],["##EC","ORG"],["##EC","ORG"],["##EC","ORG"],["United","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Qatar","MISC"],["##i","MISC"],["National Day","MISC"],["Qatar","MISC"],["##i","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["New Beginning","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Cairo","LOC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["Qatar","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Qatar","MISC"],["##i","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["MC","PER"],["##HA","PER"],["##LE","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["##lint","PER"],["Judith","PER"],["F","LOC"],["##og","LOC"],["##gy Bottom","LOC"],["Judith McHale","PER"],["Pat Kennedy","PER"],["Thomas Menighan","PER"],["AP","ORG"],["##h","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["Roger Browning","PER"],["Ann Dubas","PER"],["AP","ORG"],["##h","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["Ma","PER"],["##ura Pally","PER"],["Jeremy Curtin","PER"],["EC","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["A","ORG"],["##ppel","ORG"],["##late Court","ORG"],["Rio de Janeiro","LOC"],["Sean Goldman","PER"],["American","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["David","PER"],["New Jersey","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Hague Convention on International Child Abduction","MISC"],["Goldman","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Daily Press","ORG"],["Cuba","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["Cuba","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["St","ORG"],["##eering Group","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["-","LOC"],["Brazil","MISC"],["Me","MISC"],["of Understanding","MISC"],["##U","ORG"],["Advance","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["International Energy Affairs","ORG"],["David Goldwyn","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Energy and High Technology","ORG"],["Andre Amado","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["M","ORG"],["##O","ORG"],["##U","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Organization of American States","ORG"],["Inter American Development Bank","ORG"],["United Nations Foundation","ORG"],["M","ORG"],["##U","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Global Bioenergy Partnership GBEP","ORG"],["GB","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["G","MISC"],["##H","MISC"],["##G","MISC"],["International","MISC"],["Biofuels Forum","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Conference on Population and Development","MISC"],["Benjamin","ORG"],["Franklin Diplomatic Reception Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United","MISC"],["Nations","ORG"],["International Conference on Population and Development","MISC"],["Cairo","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["I","MISC"],["##CP","MISC"],["##D","MISC"],["UN","ORG"],["Millennium Development Goals","MISC"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Congress Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Beth Schlach","PER"],["##ter Bureau of Population Refugees and Migration","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Arms Control and","ORG"],["International Security","ORG"],["Ellen Tauscher","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["United","MISC"],["Arab Emirates","ORG"],["Agreement for Peaceful","MISC"],["Nuclear Cooperation","ORG"],["Department of State Treaty Room","ORG"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Jonathan Kaplan","PER"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Bahrain","LOC"],["National Day","MISC"],["Ham","PER"],["##ad","PER"],["Isa Al Khalifa","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Bahrain","LOC"],["Bahrain","MISC"],["##i","MISC"],["Bahrain","PER"],["##is","PER"],["Bahrain","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["National Day","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Chinese","MISC"],["Liu Xiaobo","PER"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Liu","PER"],["Government of China","ORG"],["Chinese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Serbia","LOC"],["B","PER"],["##iden","PER"],["Belgrade","LOC"],["Serbia","LOC"],["J","ORG"],["##ER","ORG"],["##EM","ORG"],["##IC","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["Washington","LOC"],["Balkans","LOC"],["Serbian","MISC"],["European Union","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["American","MISC"],["J","PER"],["##ER","PER"],["##EM","PER"],["##IC","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["International Herald Tribune","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["H","ORG"],["##IL","ORG"],["##LA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["##Y","ORG"],["R","ORG"],["##OD","ORG"],["##HA","ORG"],["##M","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Congress","ORG"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Conference on Population and Development","MISC"],["Benjamin","ORG"],["Franklin Diplomatic Reception Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United","MISC"],["Nations","ORG"],["International Conference on Population and Development","MISC"],["Cairo","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["I","MISC"],["##CP","MISC"],["##D","MISC"],["UN","ORG"],["Millennium Development Goals","MISC"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["House","ORG"],["Congress Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Beth Schlach","PER"],["##ter Bureau of Population Refugees and Migration","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["-","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Joint Economic Development Group","ORG"],["Year","MISC"],["Jerusalem","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Andy Baukol","PER"],["Treasury for International Affairs","ORG"],["Tom Engle","PER"],["Office of Monetary Affairs","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Stanley Fischer","PER"],["Bank","LOC"],["of Israel","ORG"],["Cha","PER"],["##im Shani","PER"],["Israeli","LOC"],["Ministry of Finance","ORG"],["Eugene Kandel","PER"],["Israeli","LOC"],["National Economic Council","ORG"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["is","LOC"],["##rae","LOC"],["##l","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Fi","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Jerusalem","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["United Nations Human Rights Council","ORG"],["Universal","MISC"],["Periodic Review","ORG"],["UP","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["UN","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["UN Human Rights Council","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["The","MISC"],["Universal Periodic Review","MISC"],["Human Rights Council","ORG"],["Council","ORG"],["The United States Government","ORG"],["UP","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["UP","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["K","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["##w Z","PER"],["##aw","MISC"],["Lwin","PER"],["US","ORG"],["##G","ORG"],["K","ORG"],["##ya","PER"],["##w","PER"],["Zaw Lwin","LOC"],["K","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["##w Zaw Lwin","PER"],["Burmese","MISC"],["K","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["##w Zaw Lwin","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["A","LOC"],["##b","LOC"],["##kha","LOC"],["##zia","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Nepal","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Nepal","LOC"],["United Communist Party of Nepal","ORG"],["Nepal","LOC"],["Nepali","MISC"],["Nepal","LOC"],["Nepal","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["Federal","ORG"],["Register","MISC"],["Machine Readable Visa","MISC"],["Border Crossing Card","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Mexico","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["Georgetown","LOC"],["Gaston Hall","LOC"],["J","PER"],["##as","PER"],["Foreign Service School","ORG"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["De","PER"],["##G","PER"],["##io","PER"],["##ia","PER"],["De","PER"],["##G","PER"],["##io","PER"],["##ia","PER"],["Carol Lancaster","PER"],["School of Foreign Service","ORG"],["Human Rights Institute","ORG"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Amnesty International","ORG"],["De","PER"],["##G","ORG"],["##io","PER"],["##ia","ORG"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Obama","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["K","LOC"],["##hart","LOC"],["##ou","LOC"],["##m","LOC"],["Ju","LOC"],["##ba Sudan","LOC"],["Stuttgart","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Brussels","LOC"],["Belgium","LOC"],["G","PER"],["##ration","PER"],["K","LOC"],["##hart","LOC"],["##ou","LOC"],["##m","LOC"],["Ju","LOC"],["##ba Sudan","LOC"],["National Congress Party NC","ORG"],["##P","ORG"],["Sudan People ' s Liberation Movement","ORG"],["Stuttgart","LOC"],["G","PER"],["##ration","PER"],["A","ORG"],["##F","ORG"],["##RI","ORG"],["##CO","ORG"],["##M","ORG"],["Brussels","LOC"],["G","PER"],["##ration","PER"],["European Union","ORG"],["T","ORG"],["##roi","ORG"],["##ka","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["John Bass","PER"],["Georgian","MISC"],["No","PER"],["##dar Kharshiladze","PER"],["##hi","LOC"],["##da","LOC"],["Ka","MISC"],["##rt","LOC"],["##li","MISC"],["La","LOC"],["##do Vardzelashvili","LOC"],["H","ORG"],["##AL","ORG"],["##O Trust","ORG"],["M","LOC"],["##gh","LOC"],["##vre","LOC"],["##kis","LOC"],["##i Village Go","LOC"],["##ri District","LOC"],["##hi","LOC"],["##da Kartli","LOC"],["Russia","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["H","ORG"],["##AL","ORG"],["##O","ORG"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Shi","LOC"],["##da Kartli","LOC"],["ER","MISC"],["##W","MISC"],["H","ORG"],["##AL","ORG"],["##O","ORG"],["##rt","LOC"],["Bass","PER"],["The United States","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Office of Weapons Removal and","ORG"],["##ment","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["P","PER"],[".","PER"],["J","PER"],[". Crowley","PER"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Vale","PER"],["##nz","PER"],["##uel","PER"],["##a","PER"],["Ed Romero","PER"],["O","ORG"],["##AS","ORG"],["Carmen Lomell","PER"],["Carmen","PER"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["York","LOC"],["Texas","LOC"],["Miami","LOC"],["Florida","LOC"],["Western","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Georgetown University","ORG"],["Gaston Hall","LOC"],["Georgetown","LOC"],["Edmund A. Walsh School","PER"],["of Foreign Service","ORG"],["J. DeGioia","PER"],["Georgetown","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Georgetown University","ORG"],["Hall","ORG"],["He","LOC"],["##aly Hall","LOC"],["Washington D. C.","LOC"],["Rob Mathis","PER"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["White House","ORG"],["Congress","ORG"],["Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Mathis","PER"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Democratic Society Party","ORG"],["Turkish","MISC"],["Constitutional Court","ORG"],["Constitutional Court","ORG"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["turkey","LOC"],["Turkish","MISC"],["Turkey","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Ellen Tauscher","PER"],["Polish","MISC"],["Stan","PER"],["##is","PER"],["##law Komorowski","PER"],["Agreement","MISC"],["of the","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["of","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["Republic of Poland","LOC"],["Armed Forces of the","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["of","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["Republic of Poland","LOC"],["Warsaw","LOC"],["NATO Status of Forces Agreement","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Poland","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Ball","ORG"],["##istic Missile Defense","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["##O","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["U","MISC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["-","LOC"],["Poland","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["Arturo A. Valenzuela","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Argentina Uruguay","LOC"],["Paraguay","LOC"],["South America","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["R","PER"],["##iz","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Afghanistan Pakistan","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government Accountability Office","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["mad","LOC"],["##aga","LOC"],["##sca","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["African Growth and Opportunity Act","MISC"],["Madagascar","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["Mal","ORG"],["##aga","ORG"],["##sy","ORG"],["Transit","ORG"],["##ional Government Cabinet","ORG"],["National Reconciliation Council","ORG"],["Independent Electoral Commission","ORG"],["Madagascar","LOC"],["AG","ORG"],["##OA","ORG"],["The United States Government","ORG"],["Madagascar","LOC"],["Madagascar","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["Open Skies","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Japan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Japanese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Martinez","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["Fun","PER"],["##es","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["##rt","PER"],["##ine","PER"],["##z","PER"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Fun","PER"],["##es","PER"],["Fun","PER"],["##es","PER"],["Obama","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Po","PER"],["##ros","PER"],["##hen","PER"],["##ko","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["-","ORG"],["Ukraine","ORG"],["Strategic Partnership Commission","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Lo","PER"],["##bo","PER"],["Aria","PER"],["##s","PER"],["Costa Rica","LOC"],["Martin","PER"],["##elli","PER"],["Panama","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Inter American Democratic Charter","MISC"],["O","ORG"],["##AS","ORG"],["Aria","PER"],["##s","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["San Jose","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Te","MISC"],["##gu","MISC"],["##ci","MISC"],["##gal","MISC"],["##pa","LOC"],["Aria","PER"],["##s","PER"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Lo","PER"],["##bo","PER"],["Lo","MISC"],["##bo","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United Nations","MISC"],["Universal Declaration of Human Rights","MISC"],["Universal Declaration","MISC"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["Universal Declaration","MISC"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Eleanor Roosevelt","PER"],["Universal Declaration","MISC"],["The Obama Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Human Rights Defenders Award","MISC"],["Ma","PER"],["##ks","PER"],["##hari","PER"],["##p Aushev","PER"],["Russia","LOC"],["Ma","PER"],["##ks","PER"],["##hari","PER"],["##p Aushev","PER"],["Russia","LOC"],["North","LOC"],["Caucasus","LOC"],["Human","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["C","MISC"],["##ur","MISC"],["##b","MISC"],["Bribery","PER"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Anti Corruption Day","MISC"],["Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development OECD","ORG"],["O","MISC"],["##EC","MISC"],["##D","MISC"],["Anti Bribery Convention","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Gary Locke","PER"],["O","ORG"],["##EC","ORG"],["##D","ORG"],["Angel Gurria","PER"],["International Anti Corruption Day","MISC"],["United Nations Convention against Corruption","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["Qatar","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["N","MISC"],[". Convention","MISC"],["O","ORG"],["##EC","MISC"],["##D","ORG"],["Anti Bribery Convention","MISC"],["The","MISC"],["Anti Bribery Convention","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["TO","ORG"],["##MS","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["V","ORG"],["##oil","ORG"],["##a Communication cellulaire d","ORG"],["' ha","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["u","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["s","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["owned","MISC"],["TO","ORG"],["##MS","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["V","ORG"],["##oil","ORG"],["##a Communication Cellulaire d ' Haiti","ORG"],["Trilogy International Partners","ORG"],["Haitian","MISC"],["Ch","ORG"],["##ev","ORG"],["##ron Corporation","ORG"],["C","ORG"],["##isco Systems","ORG"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["Intel Corporation","ORG"],["Costa","LOC"],["Rica","ORG"],["Mar","ORG"],["##t International","ORG"],["Jordan","LOC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Oracle Corporation","ORG"],["Romania","LOC"],["Protec","ORG"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["White","ORG"],["Russia","LOC"],["##E","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["The","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Benjamin Franklin","PER"],["Room","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Ben Franklin","PER"],["Awards for Corporate Excellence","MISC"],["AC","MISC"],["##E Awards","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Ho","PER"],["##rma","PER"],["##ts","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Gary Locke","PER"],["Obama Administration","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Dave Nelson","PER"],["California","LOC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Martinez","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["Africa","LOC"],["Me","MISC"],["##morandum","MISC"],["Trans","MISC"],["##par","MISC"],["##ency","MISC"],["Open Government","MISC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["The","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Open Government Initiative","MISC"],["Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["United","MISC"],["Nations","ORG"],["Climate Change Conference","MISC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Inter","ORG"],["##go","ORG"],["##vern","ORG"],["##mental","ORG"],["Panel on Climate Change","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["White House","LOC"],["East Anglia","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["Iraq","LOC"],["Baghdad","LOC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Iraqi","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["Tony Blair","PER"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["B","ORG"],["##LA","ORG"],["##IR","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Mitchell","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Palestinians","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["F","ORG"],["##SO","ORG"],["F","ORG"],["##SO","ORG"],["F","ORG"],["##SO","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Tocque","PER"],["##ville","LOC"],["American","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Sudan","MISC"],["##ese","MISC"],["O","LOC"],["##m","LOC"],["##du","LOC"],["##rman Sudan","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudan","MISC"],["##ese","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Inter","MISC"],["##im National Constitution","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Comprehensive Peace Agreement","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["E","PER"],["##vo Morales","PER"],["Bolivia","MISC"],["##n","MISC"],["Morales","PER"],["The United States","LOC"],["Bolivia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["Annual Conference of the Parties","MISC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Framework Convention on","MISC"],["Climate Change","MISC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration","ORG"],["NO","ORG"],["##AA","ORG"],["Earth","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["S","MISC"],["##phere","MISC"],["##C","MISC"],["##ast","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","ORG"],["##phere","ORG"],["Alexander Sandy MacDonald","PER"],["NO","ORG"],["##AA","ORG"],["Earth System Research Laboratory","ORG"],["##L","ORG"],["Boulder Colorado","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["S","MISC"],["##phere","MISC"],["##C","MISC"],["##ast","MISC"],["Discovery","ORG"],["Science","LOC"],["Center","ORG"],["Ana","LOC"],["Museum of","ORG"],["Science","LOC"],["Industry","ORG"],["Boons","ORG"],["##hof","LOC"],["##t Museum of Discovery Dayton OH","LOC"],["Maryland Science","ORG"],["Center","LOC"],["Alaska State Museum","LOC"],["Science Museum","LOC"],["Minnesota","LOC"],["Harrisonburg","ORG"],["Fi","ORG"],["Planetarium","ORG"],["He","ORG"],["##ure","ORG"],["##ka The Finnish Science Center","ORG"],["Van","ORG"],["##ta","ORG"],["##a Finland","ORG"],["NO","ORG"],["##AA","ORG"],["##L","ORG"],["MacDonald","PER"],["Earth","LOC"],["Earth","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["##phere","MISC"],["##C","MISC"],["##ast","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["NASA","ORG"],["Center","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["USA","ORG"],["##ID","ORG"],["Nancy Lindberg","PER"],["Bill Lane","PER"],["James Bell","PER"],["Richard Stearns","PER"],["Liz Shrayer","PER"],["Andrea Mitchell","PER"],["Americans","MISC"],["Andrea","PER"],["Asia","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Global Leadership Coalition","ORG"],["US","LOC"],["USA","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Associates","MISC"],["of the American Foreign Service Worldwide","ORG"],["Benjamin Franklin Diplomatic Reception Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Associates of the American Foreign Service Worldwide","ORG"],["Awards","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["Erin P. Sweeney Lagos","PER"],["Nigeria","LOC"],["Africa","LOC"],["Jan","PER"],["##M","PER"],["##ari","PER"],["##e Flattum Riemers","PER"],["Jakarta","LOC"],["Indonesia","LOC"],["East Asia","LOC"],["Pacific Lara L. Center Luxembourg Europe","ORG"],["A. Taylor Baghdad Iraq","PER"],["East","LOC"],["South East","LOC"],["Asia","ORG"],["Bern","PER"],["##ade","ORG"],["##tta","PER"],["J. Ruch Dushanbe","PER"],["South Central Asia","LOC"],["Irene Miller","PER"],["Panama","LOC"],["Panama","LOC"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense or","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Brenda Greenberg","PER"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["P","MISC"],["##EP","MISC"],["##FA","MISC"],["##R","MISC"],["Year","MISC"],["Global Context of","MISC"],["HIV","MISC"],["Global Health Initiative","MISC"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","MISC"],["Five Year","MISC"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["Global Context of HIV","MISC"],["America","LOC"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["Global Health Initiative","MISC"],["Global Health Initiative","MISC"],["P","MISC"],["##EP","MISC"],["##FA","MISC"],["##R","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["S","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["Global Health Initiative","MISC"],["Five Year","MISC"],["Year","MISC"],["Anne","ORG"],["##xes","ORG"],["George W. Bush","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 5, 2009","entities":[["Kennedy Center Honors","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin Room","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["E","MISC"],["##cumenical","MISC"],["Orthodox Church","LOC"],["Boss","PER"],["HBO","ORG"],["Carol Burnett","PER"],["Kennedy Center Honors","MISC"],["Ted Kennedy","PER"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Vic","PER"],["##ki Kennedy","PER"],["Jean Smith","PER"],["Caroline Kennedy","PER"],["Ted","PER"],["Kennedy Center","ORG"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Cold War","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Dave Brubeck","PER"],["American","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Velvet Revolutions","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Bruce","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##NT","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["##NT","MISC"],["E","ORG"],["##SF","ORG"],["McChrystal","PER"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["British","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##E DEPARTMENT","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["##NT","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AT","MISC"],["##E DEPART","MISC"],["##NT","MISC"],["##PARTMENT","MISC"],["British","MISC"],["##E","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["US","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Diploma","ORG"],["##tic","ORG"],["Reception Room","MISC"],["Magazine Publishers of America","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["The","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Magazine Publishers of America","ORG"],["Blair House","LOC"],["Diploma","LOC"],["##tic Re","LOC"],["##ception","MISC"],["Room","LOC"],["Better Homes","ORG"],["Gardens","ORG"],["Earth News Natural Home","ORG"],["Old House","LOC"],["Traditional Home","LOC"],["Blair House","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Diploma","ORG"],["##tic","ORG"],["Reception Room","MISC"],["##on","PER"],["##Y","ORG"],["NE","LOC"],["##W","LOC"],["##L","LOC"],["##Y","LOC"],["Benjamin Franklin","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["C Street","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Via","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["West Point","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Arabic","MISC"],["Dar","MISC"],["##i English Pashto","MISC"],["Urdu","MISC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["English","MISC"],["Dar","MISC"],["##i","MISC"],["##to","MISC"],["Arabic English","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Arabic","MISC"],["##ic","MISC"],["English","MISC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Latin","MISC"],["AmericaS","ORG"],["##retary","ORG"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Diploma","MISC"],["##cy Briefing Series","MISC"],["George C. Marshall","LOC"],["Conference","ORG"],["Center","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["Special","MISC"],["Press","ORG"],["Western Hemisphere","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["Press Briefing","ORG"],["Room","LOC"],["Department of State Media","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["##redentials","ORG"],["Press Briefing Room","ORG"],["Office of Regional Media Outrea","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of state","ORG"],["Yvonne Ribeiro Yemofio","PER"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Portrait Unve","MISC"],["##ony","PER"],["Colin L. Powell","PER"],["Ben Franklin Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Ben Franklin Room","LOC"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Jan","PER"],["##ine Zachria","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["E","PER"],["##rdo","PER"],["##gan","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Senior","ORG"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["E","PER"],["##rdo","PER"],["##gan","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Europe","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Iran Iraq Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan Middle East Greece European Union","ORG"],["E","PER"],["##rdo","PER"],["##gan","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Armenia","LOC"],["Zurich","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Mo","LOC"],["##ga","LOC"],["##dis","LOC"],["##hu","LOC"],["Transit","ORG"],["##ional Federal Government","ORG"],["Somali","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Somali","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["A","PER"],["S Blake","PER"],["Sri Lanka","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Treaty on","MISC"],["##uction","MISC"],["##itation of Strategic Offensive Arms","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Republic of Belarus","LOC"],["Republic of Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Union of Soviet Socialist Republics","ORG"],["##itation of Strategic Offensive Arms","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AR","MISC"],["##T Treaty","MISC"],["Republic of Belarus","LOC"],["Republic of Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["N","MISC"],["##P","MISC"],["##T","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Republic of Belarus","LOC"],["Republic of Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["Protocol to","MISC"],["ST","MISC"],["##AR","MISC"],["##T Treaty","MISC"],["N","MISC"],["##P","MISC"],["##T","MISC"],["Budapest","LOC"],["Memoranda","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Budapest","LOC"],["Memoranda","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Meeting","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Mexico","LOC"],["High Level Consultative Commission on Telecommunications HLCC","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["Philip L. Verveer","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["International Communications and Information Policy","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["##riela","PER"],["##nandez cardoso","PER"],["Mexican Ministry of Communications and Transportation","ORG"],["G","PER"],[". Osuna Jaime","PER"],["Mexico","LOC"],["Federal Telecommunications Commission","ORG"],["National Public Safety Telecommunications Council","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Advisory Committee on International Communications and Information Policy","ORG"],["H","ORG"],["##LC","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["Mexico","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["H","ORG"],["##LC","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["Directory of Bilateral","ORG"],["William H. hal","PER"],["##rigsby","PER"],["International Communications and Information","ORG"],["Office","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Kerry","PER"],["Lu","PER"],["##gar","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Congress","ORG"],["Committee","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["West Point","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["York","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Mark","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["Ho","PER"],["##l","PER"],["##brook","PER"],["##e","PER"],["Jim Steinberg","PER"],["Phil Gordon","PER"],["I","PER"],["##vo Daalder","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["Ra","PER"],["##smus","PER"],["##sen","PER"],["Gates","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Ian Kelly","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Ian Kelly","PER"],["Vale","PER"],["##nz","PER"],["##uela","PER"],["AS","ORG"],["##SI","ORG"],["##ST","ORG"],["##AN","ORG"],["##T","ORG"],["##nz","PER"],["##uel","PER"],["##a","PER"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Manuel Zelaya","PER"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Te","MISC"],["##gu","MISC"],["##ci","MISC"],["##gal","MISC"],["##pa","LOC"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["Michele","PER"],["##tti","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Te","LOC"],["##gu","LOC"],["##ci","LOC"],["##gal","LOC"],["##pa","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Le","PER"],["##w","PER"],["House Armed Services Committee","ORG"],["Brussels","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["North Atlantic Council","ORG"],["NATO Russia Council","ORG"],["IS","ORG"],["##AF","ORG"],["IS","ORG"],["##AF","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["Ra","PER"],["##smus","PER"],["##sen","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["Gates","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Mu","PER"],["##llen","PER"],["NATO","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Re","ORG"],["##ward","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["Justice Federal Bureau of Investigation","ORG"],["Pan Am","MISC"],["Flight","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["W","PER"],["##ado","PER"],["##ud Muhammad Hafiz al Turki Jamal Saeed Abdul Rahim Muhammad Abdullah Khalil Hussain ar rahayyal","PER"],["Muhammad Ahmed al Munawar","PER"],["Abu Nidal","ORG"],["District of Columbia","LOC"],["Pan American World Airways Flight 73","ORG"],["Karachi Pakistan","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Federal Bureau of Investigation","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["W","PER"],["##ado","PER"],["##ud Muhammad Hafiz al Turki","PER"],["Iraq","LOC"],["W","PER"],["##ado","PER"],["##ud Muhammad Fahd al Turk Sliman Ali Ahmad El Turki Salman Ali El Turki Bou Baker Muhammad Sulaiman Alturki","PER"],["Sul","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["##man","PER"],["Tu","PER"],["##i","PER"],["Sa","PER"],["Abdul","PER"],["Ra","PER"],["##him","PER"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Ali","PER"],["Al","PER"],["Ali","PER"],["Jamal","PER"],["Abdul","PER"],["##im","PER"],["Ali","PER"],["Al","PER"],["Muhammad","PER"],["Abdullah","PER"],["Khali","PER"],["##l Hussain","PER"],["Lebanon","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Grand Hyatt","LOC"],["US","ORG"],["##G","ORG"],["##LC","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["America","LOC"],["NBC News","ORG"],["Andrea Mitchell","PER"],["of Ceremonies","ORG"],["James Bell","PER"],["CF","ORG"],["##O","ORG"],["Boeing Company","ORG"],["Richard Stearns","PER"],["World Vision","ORG"],["NW","LOC"],["##W","LOC"],["##ashi","LOC"],["##ng","LOC"],["##ton","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Congress","ORG"],["Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Richard parkerus Global Leadership Coalition","ORG"],["Press","ORG"],["##U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["American Pakistan Foundation","ORG"],["In","ORG"],["##au","ORG"],["##gu","ORG"],["##ral Benefit","ORG"],["C","LOC"],["##ip","LOC"],["##rian","LOC"],["##i","LOC"],["New York City","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Pakistani American","MISC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Colin Powell USA","PER"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["##oe","PER"],["##en Qureshi","PER"],["Foundation","ORG"],["Pakistani americans","MISC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["American Pakistan Foundation","ORG"],["##pf","ORG"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["American Pakistan Foundation","ORG"],["East","LOC"],["York City","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Lynn","PER"],["##e Tracy","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Tracy","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["P","LOC"],["##esh","LOC"],["##awa","LOC"],["##r Pakistan","LOC"],["P","LOC"],["##esh","LOC"],["##awa","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["House","ORG"],["Congress","ORG"],["Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Lynn","PER"],["##e Tracy","PER"],["ka","PER"],["##rly","PER"],["##gas","PER"],["##h","PER"],["##lace","PER"],["##bur","PER"],["##eau","PER"],["South","LOC"],["Central Asian Affairs","ORG"],["##U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["##U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["##ynn","PER"],["TRACY","PER"],["##F","ORG"],["##OR","ORG"],["##ME","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["##pes","PER"],["##haw","PER"],["##ar pakistan","PER"],["##ynne Tracy","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["P","LOC"],["##esh","LOC"],["##awa","LOC"],["##r Pakistan","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Tracy","PER"],["Central","LOC"],["South Asia","LOC"],["As","LOC"],["Kabul","LOC"],["Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Des","ORG"],["Georgia","LOC"],["States","LOC"],["Barber","ORG"],["Ohio","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["University","ORG"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Akron","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Tim Padgett","PER"],["Time Magazine","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["SE","MISC"],["##NI","MISC"],["##OR","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Santos","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Z","LOC"],["##ela","LOC"],["##ya","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["Vale","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Is","PER"],["##t","PER"],["##van Serto Radics","PER"],["Ser","PER"],["##to Radics","PER"],["Hungarian","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Hubert","ORG"],["H. Humphrey","PER"],["Fu","MISC"],["##l","MISC"],["##bright","MISC"],["Scholar","MISC"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["Office of Alumni Affairs","ORG"],["Serto Radics","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Johns Hopkins University","ORG"],["Humphrey","ORG"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Us","LOC"],["##z","LOC"],["##ka","LOC"],["Roma","LOC"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Us","LOC"],["##z","LOC"],["##ka","LOC"],["Roma","MISC"],["Ser","MISC"],["##to Radics","MISC"],["Us","LOC"],["##z","LOC"],["##ka","LOC"],["European","MISC"],["Union United States","ORG"],["Democracy","MISC"],["and Civil","ORG"],["Society Award","MISC"],["Roma","MISC"],["Ser","PER"],["##to Radics","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["University of Mississippi","ORG"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Ser","PER"],["##to Radics","PER"],["Mississippi","LOC"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Hungary","LOC"],["European Union","ORG"],["Ser","ORG"],["Ra","ORG"],["Hungarian","MISC"],["Region","ORG"],["European Union","ORG"],["Commission","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 2, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["International Day","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 2, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Awards","MISC"],["Excellence","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin Room","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["AC","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["AC","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["AC","MISC"],["##E","MISC"],["Ch","ORG"],["##ev","ORG"],["##ron Corporation","ORG"],["Philippines","LOC"],["C","ORG"],["##isco Systems","ORG"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["C","ORG"],["##um","ORG"],["##mins China Intel Corporation","ORG"],["Costa Rica","LOC"],["Mar","ORG"],["##riot","ORG"],["##t International","ORG"],["Jordan","LOC"],["Office","ORG"],["##net Staples","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Oracle Corporation","ORG"],["Romania","LOC"],["Pro","ORG"],["##tec","ORG"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["White","PER"],["Case","ORG"],["Russia","LOC"],["Robert D. Hormats","PER"],["Economic Energy and Agricultural Affairs","ORG"],["AC","ORG"],["##E","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[". Embassies","LOC"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Press","ORG"],["Contact","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["Kerry Humphrey Bureau of Economic Energy and Business Affairs","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["Advisory","ORG"],["Committee on","ORG"],["Historical Diplomatic Documentation","MISC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["D. C.","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["National Archives and Records Administration","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Margaret Morrissey","PER"],["Office of","ORG"],["US","LOC"],["Margaret Morrissey","PER"],["Edward Brynn","PER"],["Advisory","ORG"],["on","ORG"],["Historical","ORG"],["Diplomatic Documentation","MISC"],["Department of State Office of the Historian","ORG"],["D. C.","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Brussels","LOC"],["North Atlantic Council NAC","ORG"],["NATO Headquarters","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["Ra","PER"],["##smus","PER"],["##sen","PER"],["Belgian","MISC"],["Yves Leterme","PER"],["Steven Vanackere","PER"],["EU","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["Eric Goosby","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Global","ORG"],["AIDS","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["Go","PER"],["##os","PER"],["##by","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Tu","MISC"],["##ber","MISC"],["##cu","MISC"],["##los","MISC"],["##is","MISC"],["Mal","LOC"],["##aria","LOC"],["Go","PER"],["##os","PER"],["##by","PER"],["GO","PER"],["##OS","PER"],["##B","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["State Department USAID","ORG"],["CD","ORG"],["##C Department of Defense Peace Corps","ORG"],["Bush","PER"],["Congress","ORG"],["P","MISC"],["##EP","MISC"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["African","MISC"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Kenya","LOC"],["Committee of Experts","ORG"],["Kenya","LOC"],["Kenya","LOC"],["Kenyan","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Kenyan","MISC"],["Ki","PER"],["##ba","PER"],["##ki","PER"],["O","PER"],["##ding","PER"],["##a","PER"],["Parliament","ORG"],["The United States","LOC"],["Kenyan","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Tu","MISC"],["##ber","MISC"],["##cu","MISC"],["##los","MISC"],["##is","MISC"],["Mal","ORG"],["##aria","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","LOC"],[". Government","ORG"],["Global Fund The U.","ORG"],["S. Government","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["US","MISC"],["$","MISC"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["The Global Fund","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["US","MISC"],["Global","ORG"],["Global","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["World AIDS Day","MISC"],["Five Year","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["Five Year","MISC"],["Global Health Initiative","MISC"],["Year","MISC"],["George W. Bush","PER"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","ORG"],["##FA","ORG"],["##R","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Car","LOC"],["##tage","LOC"],["##na","LOC"],["Second Review Conference","MISC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Use","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Review Conference","MISC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Ottawa","LOC"],["U","PER"],["##ri","PER"],["##be","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Administration","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Am","MISC"],["##ended Mines Protocol to","MISC"],["Convention on Certain Conventional Weapons","MISC"],["Administration","ORG"],["Review Conference","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["U","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Em","MISC"],["##ira","MISC"],["##ti","MISC"],["United Arab Emirates","LOC"],["National Day","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Cairo","LOC"],["UAE","LOC"],["UAE","LOC"],["she","PER"],["##ik","PER"],["##h Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan","PER"],["she","PER"],["##ik","PER"],["##h Khalifa Bin Zayed Al Nahyan","PER"],["she","PER"],["##ik","PER"],["##h Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum","PER"],["Supreme Council of the Federation","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["UAE","LOC"],["Em","MISC"],["##ira","MISC"],["##ti","MISC"],["National Day","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia","ORG"],["Second Review Conference","MISC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Car","LOC"],["##tage","LOC"],["##na Colombia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["S","LOC"],[". Government","ORG"],["Colombian","MISC"],["Government","ORG"],["Presidential","MISC"],["Program for","ORG"],["Comprehensive Action Against Anti personnel Mines","ORG"],["Colombian","MISC"],["The","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Colombia Humanitarian Demining Planning Workshop","ORG"],["Bo","LOC"],["##got","LOC"],["##a","LOC"],["Colombian","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Organization of American States","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Colombian","MISC"],["Centro Integral de Rehabilitacion de Colombia","ORG"],["##c","ORG"],["See","MISC"],["##ds of Hope","ORG"],["Colombia","LOC"],["The Polus Center","ORG"],["Colombian","MISC"],["Information Management and Mine Action Program","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Agency for International Development","ORG"],["Mercy Corps","ORG"],["Colombian","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Southern Command","ORG"],["The United States","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["K","ORG"],["##EL","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["West Hemisphere Affairs","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["AS","ORG"],["##SI","ORG"],["##ST","ORG"],["##AN","ORG"],["##T","ORG"],["##ale","PER"],["##nz","PER"],["##uel","PER"],["##a","PER"],["Western Hemisphere Affairs","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["P","PER"],["##ep","PER"],["##e Lobo","PER"],["sa","PER"],["##nto","PER"],["##s","PER"],["Ham","PER"],["A","PER"],["##vila","PER"],["Martinez","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Te","MISC"],["##gu","MISC"],["##ci","LOC"],["##gal","MISC"],["##pa","LOC"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["San Jose Accords","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["San","MISC"],["Spanish","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["Jacob J. Lew","PER"],["Eric Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[". Global","ORG"],["AIDS","MISC"],["World AIDS Day","MISC"],["The World Bank","ORG"],["Keeping the Promise","MISC"],["HIV AIDS Food Security","ORG"],["Mat","ORG"],["##ern","ORG"],["##al and Child Health","ORG"],["Le","PER"],["##w","PER"],["Go","PER"],["##os","PER"],["##by","PER"],["Michel Kazatchkine","PER"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Tu","MISC"],["##ber","MISC"],["##cu","MISC"],["##los","MISC"],["##is","MISC"],["Mal","PER"],["##aria Joy Phumaphi","PER"],["World Bank","ORG"],["Julian Schweitzer","PER"],["Human Development","ORG"],["population The World Bank","ORG"],["The World Bank","ORG"],["World Bank","ORG"],["H","LOC"],["St","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["N","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["W","LOC"],[". Washington","LOC"],["RS","ORG"],["##VP","ORG"],["Jennifer Peterson Office","PER"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["pet","PER"],["##erson","PER"],["##j","PER"],["##l","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["R","PER"],["##udd","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Oval Office","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Australia","LOC"],["##udd","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Australia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[". Humanitarian Mine Action Program","MISC"],["Department of State Department of Defense u","ORG"],[".","LOC"],["s","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["International Development","ORG"],["Centers for Disease Control and Prevention","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[". Humanitarian Mine Action Program","MISC"],["Costa Rica Djibo","LOC"],["##uti Guatemala Honduras Kosovo Macedonia Namibia Rwanda","LOC"],["Sur","LOC"],["##iname","LOC"],["The United States","LOC"],["U","MISC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["Humanitarian Mine Action","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Bosnia Colombia","LOC"],["Iraq Laos","LOC"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Convention on Certain Conventional Weapons CCW","MISC"],["Am","MISC"],["##ended Protocol II","MISC"],["Protocol V","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Organization of the Islamic Conference O","ORG"],["##IC","ORG"],["Jo","ORG"],["##ining Forces","ORG"],["Pol","MISC"],["##io","MISC"],["UN","ORG"],["##IC","ORG"],["##EF","ORG"],["New York City","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Cairo","LOC"],["O","ORG"],["##IC","ORG"],["UN","ORG"],["##IC","ORG"],["##EF","ORG"],["Ann M. Veneman U.","PER"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Economic and Social Council of the United Nations","ORG"],["Frederick D. Barton","PER"],["Permanent Observer Mission of the Organization of the Islamic Conference","ORG"],["United","ORG"],["Nations","LOC"],["New York","LOC"],["Wah","PER"],["##ab","ORG"],["William Foege","PER"],["Melinda Gates Foundation","ORG"],["Bruce Aylward","PER"],["Global Polio Eradication Initiative","ORG"],["World Health Organization","ORG"],["Jim Lacy","PER"],["R","ORG"],["##ota","ORG"],["##ry International","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Raza Tarar","PER"],["Pakistan","ORG"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Erin McLinn mclinnej","PER"],["Bureau of International Organization Affairs Office of Public Affairs and Outreach","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["Mu","LOC"],["##ji","LOC"],["##ca","PER"],["Uruguay","LOC"],["Uruguay","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Mu","PER"],["##ji","PER"],["##ca","PER"],["Uruguay","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 29, 2009","entities":[["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Americas","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Te","MISC"],["##gu","MISC"],["##ci","MISC"],["##gal","MISC"],["##pa","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["Ian Kelly","PER"],["Ian Kelly","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["I","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["##EA","ORG"],["Vienna","LOC"],["SE","ORG"],["##NI","ORG"],["##OR","ORG"],["##TI","ORG"],["##ON","ORG"],["OF","ORG"],["##FI","ORG"],["##AL","ORG"],["International Atomic Energy Agency Board of Governors","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["I","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["##EA","ORG"],["UN Security Council","ORG"],["I","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["##EA","ORG"],["N","MISC"],["##P","MISC"],["##T","ORG"],["Mohamed ElBaradei","PER"],["I","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["##EA","ORG"],["Tehran","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[". Russia China","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Britain","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Russia","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Vienna","LOC"],["Mohamed","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Barbados","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Consular Agency","ORG"],["Bridget","LOC"],["##own","LOC"],["Eastern Caribbean","LOC"],["Barbados","LOC"],["Barbados","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Organization of American States","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Te","LOC"],["##gu","LOC"],["##ci","LOC"],["##gal","LOC"],["##pa","LOC"],["Z","PER"],["##ela","PER"],["##ya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Supreme Electoral Tribunal","ORG"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"],["Te","MISC"],["##gu","MISC"],["##ci","MISC"],["##gal","MISC"],["##pa","LOC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##du","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudan","LOC"],["K","LOC"],["##hart","LOC"],["##ou","LOC"],["##m Abyei","LOC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["K","LOC"],["##hart","LOC"],["##ou","LOC"],["##m","LOC"],["Comprehensive Peace Agreement","MISC"],["National Congress Party NCP","ORG"],["Sudan People ' s Liberation Movement","ORG"],["Southern Sudan","LOC"],["A","LOC"],["##by","LOC"],["##ei","LOC"],["G","PER"],["##ration","PER"],["A","LOC"],["##by","LOC"],["##ei","LOC"],["Permanent Court of Arbitration","ORG"],["##ca","ORG"],["PC","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["Chad sudan","LOC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["K","LOC"],["##hart","LOC"],["##ou","LOC"],["##m Abyei","LOC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["Sudan","MISC"],["##ese","MISC"],["Sudan","MISC"],["##ese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 26, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Sa","MISC"],["##hra","MISC"],["##wi","MISC"],["Am","PER"],["##ina","PER"],["##to","PER"],["##u Haidar","PER"],["Robert","MISC"],["F.","PER"],["Kennedy","MISC"],["Train Foundation","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["Mitchell","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Mitchell","PER"],["MIT","ORG"],["##CH","ORG"],["##EL","ORG"],["##L","ORG"],["Net","PER"],["##any","PER"],["##ahu","PER"],["is","MISC"],["##rae","MISC"],["##li","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Administration","ORG"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Arab States","LOC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Arab","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Israel","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["Arabic","MISC"],["Hebrew","MISC"],["is","LOC"],["##rae","LOC"],["##l","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["##inian","MISC"],["Palestinian","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Jewish","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["HIV AIDS","MISC"],["Health and Human Services","ORG"],["Kathleen Sebelius","PER"],["Eric P. Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Valerie Jarrett","PER"],["State Department Press Corp","ORG"],["White House","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Social Security","MISC"],["Eastern","MISC"],["Obama Administration","PER"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Health and Human Services","ORG"],["Kathleen Sebelius","PER"],["Eric P. Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Valerie Jarrett","PER"],["Jeffrey S. Crowley","PER"],["White","PER"],["House Office of National AIDS Policy","ORG"],["Eisenhower Executive Office","ORG"],["Eastern","MISC"],["Eisenhower Executive Office Building","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["India","LOC"],["Singh","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["India","MISC"],["Nuclear Cooperation Agreement","MISC"],["Singh","PER"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["India","MISC"],["Civil Nuclear Cooperation Initiative","ORG"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["White House","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["UN Framework Convention on Climate Change","MISC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["Denmark","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["The","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["Bella Conference","ORG"],["Center","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Earth","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Center","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Center","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Federal","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Eli","MISC"],["##mination","MISC"],["Violence Against Women","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Mel","PER"],["##anne Verveer","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Democratic","MISC"],["Republic","MISC"],["Congo","LOC"],["United","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["Department of State Advisory Committee on International Law","ORG"],["George Washington University Law School","ORG"],["Michael K. Young","PER"],["Faculty Conference Center","ORG"],["St","LOC"],["Washington D. C","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Harold H. Koh","PER"],["International Criminal Court","ORG"],["International Court of Justice","ORG"],["Mexico","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["of","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["Office of the Legal Adviser","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Co","LOC"],["##te d ' Ivoire","LOC"],["' ivo","MISC"],["Co","LOC"],["##te d ' Ivoire","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Co","ORG"],["##te d ' Ivoire","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["Bob","PER"],["Krishna","PER"],["Ah","PER"],["##lu","PER"],["##walia","PER"],["India","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["Kaur","PER"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["Joe Biden","PER"],["Jill Biden","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Senate","ORG"],["India","LOC"],["Friends of India Caucus","ORG"],["Senate","ORG"],["B","PER"],["##iden","PER"],["Senate Foreign Relations Committee","ORG"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Obama","ORG"],["Administration","MISC"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Krishna","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["Re","ORG"],["##ward","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["For Justice Federal Bureau of Investigation","ORG"],["Hu","PER"],["##say","PER"],["##n Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Hu","PER"],["##say","PER"],["##n Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["Abu Ibrahim Husayn Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["FBI","ORG"],["Pan American World Airways","ORG"],["Al Umari","PER"],["Na","LOC"],["##rita Japan","LOC"],["Honolulu Hawaii","LOC"],["Al Umari","PER"],["District of Columbia","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". District Court","ORG"],["Mohammad Rashed","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["al Umari","PER"],["Government of France","ORG"],["Marks and Spencer Department","ORG"],["Paris","LOC"],["Le","ORG"],["##umi Bank","ORG"],["Al Umari","PER"],["J","LOC"],["##af","LOC"],["##fa","LOC"],["British","MISC"],["Palestine","LOC"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["K","LOC"],["##GB","ORG"],["German","MISC"],["Red","ORG"],["Irish","MISC"],["Republican","MISC"],["Basque","MISC"],["Japanese","MISC"],["Red","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Hu","PER"],["##say","PER"],["##n Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["Abu Ibrahim","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Second Review Conference","MISC"],["Convention","MISC"],["Use","MISC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Car","LOC"],["##tage","LOC"],["##na Colombia","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["State Party","ORG"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["South African","MISC"],["Pre","LOC"],["##toria South Africa","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Bonnie Jenkins","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["South Africa","MISC"],["##proliferation and","MISC"],["##sarmament","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Robert Einhorn","PER"],["U","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["S","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["South Africa","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 23, 2009","entities":[["Bulgarian","MISC"],["Z","PER"],["##hel","PER"],["##eva","PER"],["Europe","LOC"],["Euro Atlantic","MISC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Central","LOC"],["Eastern Europe","LOC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Bulgarian","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["European Union","ORG"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Eurasian","MISC"],["Richard Morningstar","PER"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["United States","ORG"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Bulgarian","MISC"],["Clinton","PER"],["United States","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 23, 2009","entities":[["K","PER"],["##EL","PER"],["##L","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["K","PER"],["##EL","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["Iran","LOC"],["##EL","PER"],["K","PER"],["##EL","PER"],["##L","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["Wood","PER"],["P","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["Iran","LOC"],["K","PER"],["##EL","PER"],["##L","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["Kabul","LOC"],["K","PER"],["##EL","PER"],["##L","PER"],["K","PER"],["##EL","PER"],["##L","PER"],["##Y","PER"],["Brussels","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["I","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["##EA","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Council","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 23, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Asia","LOC"],["Kabul","LOC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Richard Holbrooke","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Richard","PER"],["Richard","PER"],["##OL","ORG"],["##BR","PER"],["##O","PER"],["##OK","PER"],["##E","PER"],[".","PER"],["J","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["der","PER"],["##eck","PER"],["Der","PER"],["##eck Hogan","PER"],["State Department Foreign Service","ORG"],["MS","MISC"],["Maureen White","PER"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["USA","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["Michele Bond","PER"],["Directorate for Overseas Citizens Services","ORG"],["Office of Policy Coordination and Public Outreach","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Bureau of Consular Affairs","ORG"],["Office of Overseas Citizens Services","ORG"],["Bond","PER"],["Overseas Citizens Services","ORG"],["Bureau of Consular Affairs","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["The Hague Convention","MISC"],["##option","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["United","LOC"],["Hague","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["Michele","PER"],["##tti","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["Brazil","MISC"],["Joint Commission","ORG"],["John Holdren","PER"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["White House Office of Science and Technology Policy","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Sergio Rezende","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Ministry for Science and Technology","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Nina Fedoroff","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Agency for International Development","ORG"],["John Holdren","PER"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Re","PER"],["##zen","PER"],["##de","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["u","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["s","MISC"],[".","MISC"],["-","MISC"],["bra","MISC"],["##lian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Agency for International Development","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Agency for International Cooperation","ORG"],["Brazilian Agricultural Research Corporation em","ORG"],["##bra","ORG"],["##pa","ORG"],["m","ORG"],["##oz","ORG"],["##am","ORG"],["##bi","ORG"],["##que The Governments of","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Joint Commission","ORG"],["Patrick Gallagher","PER"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". National Institute of Standards and Technology","ORG"],["Jo","PER"],["##ao Alziro herz da Jornada","PER"],["Brazilian National Institute of Metro","ORG"],["Ministry of Development Industry","ORG"],["Foreign","ORG"],["chemical","ORG"],["Richard","ORG"],["Wyatt","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["National Institutes","ORG"],["F","ORG"],["International Center","ORG"],["Jorge","ORG"],["Al","ORG"],["G","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Federal","ORG"],["Agency","ORG"],["Foundation","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["i","LOC"],["##ran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iranian","MISC"],["Government of Iran","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN Special Rapporteur","ORG"],["Special Rapport","ORG"],["##eur","MISC"],["Special Rapporteur","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Working Group on","ORG"],["or In","ORG"],["##ntary","ORG"],["##ce","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["M","PER"],["##c","PER"],["##C","PER"],["##hr","PER"],["##ys","PER"],["##tal","PER"],["rod","PER"],["##rig","PER"],["##ue","PER"],["##z","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["American","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Jack Lew","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["At","LOC"],["##ter","LOC"],["##bury Muscatatuck","LOC"],["Center","ORG"],["Complex Operations CA","ORG"],["Indiana","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["NATO","ORG"],["International Security Assistance Force IS","ORG"],["##AF","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["CA","ORG"],["State Department USAID","ORG"],["Department of State USAID","ORG"],["Department of Agriculture","ORG"],["Afghan","MISC"],["CA MCCO","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Yemen","MISC"],["##i","MISC"],["G","LOC"],["##uant","LOC"],["##ana","LOC"],["##mo Detention Facility","LOC"],["Yemen","MISC"],["##i","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Ham","PER"],["##id Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["U","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Ham","PER"],["##id Karzai","PER"],["British","MISC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Clinton","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Radio Azadi","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Ham","PER"],["##id Karzai","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Government","ORG"],["Taliban","MISC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Taliban","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["Taliban","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Van Rompuy","PER"],["Ashton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iranian","MISC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Javier Solana","PER"],["Ben","PER"],["##ita Ferrero Waldner","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["##lint","PER"],["##on","PER"],["E","PER"],["##ike","PER"],["##n","PER"],["##berry","PER"],["M","PER"],["##c","PER"],["##C","PER"],["##hr","PER"],["##ys","PER"],["##tal","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["E","PER"],["##ike","PER"],["##n","PER"],["##berry","PER"],["M","PER"],["##c","PER"],["##C","PER"],["##hr","PER"],["##ys","PER"],["##tal","PER"],["Ho","PER"],["##l","PER"],["##brook","PER"],["##e","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Government","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["USA","LOC"],["Kabul","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Canada","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Canada","LOC"],["The","MISC"],["Air Quality Agreement","MISC"],["Government of Canada","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Ba","LOC"],["##gram","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Republic of Suriname","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"],["sur","LOC"],["##iname","LOC"],["Sur","LOC"],["##iname","LOC"],["Independence Day Marathon","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["South Dakota","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["sur","LOC"],["##iname","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudan","LOC"],["K","LOC"],["##hart","LOC"],["##ou","LOC"],["##m Abyei","LOC"],["Dar","LOC"],["##fu","LOC"],["##r","LOC"],["G","PER"],["##ration","PER"],["A","LOC"],["##by","LOC"],["##ei","LOC"],["Permanent Court of Arbitration","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Black Consciousness Day","MISC"],["Z","MISC"],["##um","MISC"],["##bi","MISC"],["dos","PER"],["##ares","PER"],["Q","LOC"],["##uil","LOC"],["##omb","LOC"],["##o","LOC"],["Z","PER"],["##um","PER"],["##bi","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afro","MISC"],["Salvador da Bahia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[". Brazil","LOC"],["Afro","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["Overseas Security Advisory Council","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["e","PER"],["##ike","PER"],["##n","PER"],["##berry","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["E","PER"],["##ike","PER"],["##n","PER"],["##berry","PER"],["E","PER"],["##ike","PER"],["##n","PER"],["##berry","PER"],["Frank","PER"],["Tony","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Ka","PER"],["##rz","PER"],["##ai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["US","LOC"],["Provincial Reconstruction Teams","ORG"],["Embassy","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["-","LOC"],["Brazil","MISC"],["Joint","MISC"],["Commission","ORG"],["Meeting on","MISC"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["Cooperation","MISC"],["Lo","LOC"],["##y Henderson Auditorium","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["John Holdren","PER"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["White House Office of Science and Technology Policy","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Sergio Rezende","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Ministry for Science and Technology","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Joint Commission","ORG"],["Nina Fedoroff","PER"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["Re","PER"],["##zen","PER"],["##de","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Hold","PER"],["##ren","PER"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense or","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Alice Chu Department","PER"],["of State Bureau of Oceans International","ORG"],["Environmental","ORG"],["Scientific Affairs","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Exchange","MISC"],["##s","MISC"],["##C","MISC"],["##on","MISC"],["##nect Video Contest","MISC"],["World","MISC"],["Exchange","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["##on","ORG"],["##nect","ORG"],["The Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["EC","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Exchange","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["##C","MISC"],["##on","MISC"],["##nect","MISC"],["Exchange","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["##on","ORG"],["##nect","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Exchange","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["##on","ORG"],["##nect","ORG"],["Exchange","ORG"],["##s","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["##on","ORG"],["##nect","ORG"],["EC","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["Jay","PER"],["Craven Independent Filmmaker","ORG"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["A","ORG"],["##FI","ORG"],["Global Cultural Exchange","ORG"],["V","PER"],["##ass","PER"],["##ili","PER"],["##os Karamitsanis","PER"],["Platform","PER"],["##a International Film Festival","ORG"],["Urban Cultural Company","ORG"],["Josef Frank Madisia","PER"],["National Art Gallery Namibia","ORG"],["Rod","PER"],["##ol","PER"],["##fo Molina","PER"],["El Salvador","PER"],["Visual Arts","MISC"],["##l","MISC"],["Hi","PER"],["##nd Shoufani","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Office of Protocol","ORG"],["The Office of the Chief of Protocol","ORG"],["White House","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Czechoslovakia","LOC"],["Polish","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Prague","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Czech Republic","LOC"],["Slovakia","LOC"],["Tomas Masaryk","PER"],["Middle Europe","LOC"],["Czech Republic","LOC"],["Slovakia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Tropical Storm Ida","MISC"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["San Salvador","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States Government","ORG"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Agency for International Development","ORG"],["u","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["s","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of Defense","ORG"],["Southern Command","ORG"],["us","ORG"],["##aid","ORG"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Armed Forces","ORG"],["USA","MISC"],["##ID","MISC"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["us","ORG"],["##aid","ORG"],["Miami","LOC"],["USA","ORG"],["##ID","ORG"],["us","ORG"],["##aid","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","LOC"],[". Southern Command","ORG"],["Human","MISC"],["##itarian","MISC"],["Assistance","ORG"],["Projects","MISC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Southern Command","ORG"],["Joint Task Force Bravo","ORG"],["Hon","LOC"],["##du","LOC"],["##ran Air Force Base","LOC"],["Can","ORG"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Salvador","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Greek","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Government","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Institute of International Education IIE","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["The","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Public Diplomacy","ORG"],["Public Affairs","ORG"],["Judith A. McHale","PER"],["National Press Club","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Education","ORG"],["##US","ORG"],["##A","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of Commerce","ORG"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["State","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["EC","ORG"],["United","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Government of","ORG"],["Kosovo","LOC"],["Kosovo","LOC"],["Kosovo","LOC"],["Serb","MISC"],["Kosovo","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["Open Doors","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["The Institute of International Education","ORG"],["U","ORG"],[".","ORG"],["S","ORG"],[". Department of State","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["Public Diplomacy","ORG"],["Public Affairs","ORG"],["Judith A. McHale","PER"],["National Press Club","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["DC","ORG"],["International Education","MISC"],["The State Department","ORG"],["Fu","MISC"],["##l","MISC"],["##bright Program","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["##min","MISC"],["International Scholarship","MISC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["Ireland","LOC"],["Austria","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Costa Rica Japan Argentina","ORG"],["South Africa","LOC"],["U","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[".","LOC"],["United Kingdom","LOC"],["Italy Spain","LOC"],["France","LOC"],["Western Europe","LOC"],["English","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Africa","LOC"],["Asia","LOC"],["Latin America","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"]]}
