{"publish_date":"December 31, 2009","entities":[["Michelle Kwan","PER"],["Korea","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["Michelle","PER"],["Seoul Pyeongchang","LOC"],["Goyang","LOC"],["Olympics","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Korea","LOC"],["Yongsan Military Garrison","LOC"],["Darlene Kirk","PER"],["Brian Gibel","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Seoul","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 31, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"],["Nestor Tedesco","PER"],["Argentine","MISC"],["Fulbright Foreign Student Program","MISC"],["Tedesco","PER"],["Argentinean","MISC"],["Argentine","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Tedesco","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Boston","LOC"],["Fulbright Program","MISC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Buenos Aires Colon Theater","ORG"],["National Art Institute University","ORG"],["Tedesco","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Zonas de Accion Prioritaria","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Tedesco","PER"],["Tedesco","PER"],["Argentina","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Tedesco","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Villa","LOC"],["31","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Joshua Bell Tedesco","PER"],["Fu","ORG"],["##bright","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["Office","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 30, 2009","entities":[["Burma","LOC"],["British","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"],["Burma","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Burma","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Burmese","MISC"],["Burmese","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 29, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Republic of Haiti","LOC"],["Haiti","LOC"],["Toussaint Louverture Jean Jacques Dessalines","PER"],["Alexandre Petion","PER"],["Haitian Americans","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Haiti","LOC"],["Haitian","MISC"],["Haiti","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 29, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Chad","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Chadian","MISC"],["Moussa Faki","PER"],["Sudanese","MISC"],["Ghazi Salahuddin","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Chad","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["N ' Djamena Chad","LOC"],["Darfur Peace Process","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Chad","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 28, 2009","entities":[["Ian","PER"],["KELL","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["London","LOC"],["London","LOC"],["Nigeria","LOC"],["Abuja","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"],["London","LOC"],["KELL","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["KELL","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 27, 2009","entities":[["Royal","ORG"],["Thai","MISC"],["Government","ORG"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Office of the United Nations","ORG"],["Royal","ORG"],["Thai","MISC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Lao People ' s Democratic Republic","LOC"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Huay Nam Khao Camp","LOC"],["Petchabun","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["Royal Thai Government","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["H","MISC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Nong Khai","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["Office","ORG"],["Thailand","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"],["Thai","MISC"],["Eric Schwartz","PER"],["##ail","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Thailand","LOC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Royal Thai","ORG"],["Royal","ORG"],["Thai","MISC"],["Lao Hmong","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 24, 2009","entities":[["Sean Goldman","PER"],["David Goldman","PER"],["Rio de Janeiro","LOC"],["New Jersey","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Hague Convention on International Child Abduction","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Chinese","MISC"],["Liu Xiaobo","PER"],["Liu","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Covenant on Civil and Political Rights","MISC"],["China","LOC"],["Liu","PER"],["Chinese","MISC"],["China","LOC"],["Chinese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Iranian","MISC"],["Amir Hossein Ardebili","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Tandja","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Niger","LOC"],["Government of","ORG"],["Niger","LOC"],["Niger","LOC"],["Niger","LOC"],["Niger","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Richard M. Nixon","PER"],["Gerald R. Ford","PER"],["Richard Nixon","PER"],["Bretton Woods","MISC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Smithsonian Agreement","MISC"],["Group of Seven G - 7","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["White House","LOC"],["Trade Act of 1974","MISC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Soviet Union","LOC"],["Jewish","MISC"],["Tokyo Round","MISC"],["General Agreement on Tariffs","MISC"],["and","ORG"],["Trade","MISC"],["GATT","ORG"],["Nixon","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["North South","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["Brazil","LOC"],["Brasilia","LOC"],["Rio de Janeiro","LOC"],["Goldman","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Sean Goldman","PER"],["David","PER"],["Kingston Jamaica","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Mark","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 23, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["National Assembly","ORG"],["Southern Sudan","LOC"],["NCP","ORG"],["NCP","ORG"],["SPLM","ORG"],["Abyei","LOC"],["Southern Sudan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["National Security Act","MISC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 21, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Maksharip Aushev","PER"],["Nazran Ingushetia","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Aushev","PER"],["Russia","LOC"],["North Caucasus","LOC"],["Aushev","PER"],["Russian","MISC"],["North Caucasus","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 19, 2009","entities":[["Royal Government of","ORG"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["Uighur","MISC"],["China","LOC"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Cambodian","MISC"],["Office","ORG"],["UN","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["Cambodia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["China","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN Third Committee","ORG"],["Iranian","MISC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Romania","LOC"],["Central Europe","LOC"],["Timisoara","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"],["Romanian","MISC"],["European Union","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Romania","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Kerri Ann Jones","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["A","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["National Strategy for Pandemic Influenza","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Jones","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Jones","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Kerri Ann Jones","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Department","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["DipNote","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["DipNote","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["DipNote","ORG"],["Twitter","ORG"],["YouTube","ORG"],["DipNote","ORG"],["Sudan Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Global Women","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Richard Nixon","PER"],["Gerald Ford","PER"],["Nixon","PER"],["Nixon","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Antarctic","LOC"],["Nixon","PER"],["Ford","PER"],["Antarctic","LOC"],["Nixon Ford","PER"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Morocco","LOC"],["Aminatou Haidar","PER"],["Robert F","PER"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Spain","LOC"],["Moroccan","MISC"],["Western Sahara","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Ban Ki Moon","PER"],["UN","MISC"],["Manhasset","MISC"],["Christopher Ross","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Copenhagen","LOC"],["Todd Stern","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Todd Stern","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Recovery Act","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Major Economies Forum on Energy and Climate","ORG"],["G20","ORG"],["Asian Pacific Economic Cooperation","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 17, 2009","entities":[["Horn of Africa","LOC"],["Somali","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["International Maritime Organization","ORG"],["United Nations Office on Drugs and Crime","ORG"],["Contact Group on","ORG"],["Pi","MISC"],["Coast","LOC"],["of","ORG"],["Somalia","LOC"],["Somalia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Ministry of External Relations of","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Ministry of External Relations of","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["Brasilia","LOC"],["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Brasilia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S.","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["U","MISC"],["S. - Brazil","MISC"],["Joint Commission","ORG"],["Meeting JCM","MISC"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["JCM","MISC"],["##o","ORG"],["##sil","ORG"],["##vo","ORG"],["American Council on Competitiveness","ORG"],["Consultative Committee on Agriculture","ORG"],["Brazil","LOC"],["CCA","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["CCA","ORG"],["Codex Ali","ORG"],["UN FAO","ORG"],["Codex Committee","ORG"],["OECD","ORG"],["OECD","ORG"],["OECD","ORG"],["United","ORG"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Qatari","MISC"],["National Day","MISC"],["Qatari","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["New Beginning","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Cairo","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Qatar","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Qatari","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["MC","PER"],["##HA","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["clinton","PER"],["Judith","PER"],["Foggy Bottom","LOC"],["Judith McHale","PER"],["Pat Kennedy","PER"],["Thomas Menighan","PER"],["APhA","ORG"],["Roger Browning","PER"],["Ann Dubas","PER"],["APhA","ORG"],["Maura Pally","PER"],["Jeremy Curtin","PER"],["ECA","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["War","MISC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["Union","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Appellate Court","ORG"],["Rio de Janeiro","LOC"],["Sean Goldman","PER"],["American","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["David","PER"],["New Jersey","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Hague Convention on International Child Abduction","MISC"],["Goldman","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Daily Press","ORG"],["Cuba","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],[". Government","ORG"],["Cuba","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Group","ORG"],["U","MISC"],["S.","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Memorandum of Understanding M","MISC"],["Advance","ORG"],["Cooperation","MISC"],["B","MISC"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["David Goldwyn","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Energy and","ORG"],["Technology","ORG"],["Andre Amado","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Organization of American States","ORG"],["Inter American Development Bank","ORG"],["United Nations Foundation","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Global","MISC"],["B","ORG"],["##io","MISC"],["##energy Partnership GBEP","ORG"],["GBEP","ORG"],["International Biofuels Forum","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Conference on Population and Development I","MISC"],["##CP","ORG"],["##D","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin","LOC"],["Re","LOC"],["Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United","MISC"],["Nations","ORG"],["International Conference on Population and Development","MISC"],["Cairo","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["ICPD","MISC"],["UN","ORG"],["Millennium Development Goals","MISC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Schl","ORG"],["##ter Bureau of Population Refugees and Migration U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 16, 2009","entities":[["Arms Control and International Security","ORG"],["Ellen Tauscher","PER"],["United States United Arab Emirates","LOC"],["Agreement for Peaceful Nuclear Cooperation","MISC"],["Department of State Treaty Room","ORG"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Jonathan Kaplan","PER"],["Office of Press Relations","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Bahrain","LOC"],["National Day","MISC"],["Hamad","PER"],["Isa Al Khalifa","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Bahrain","LOC"],["Bahraini","MISC"],["Bahrain","MISC"],["Bahrain","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["National Day","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Chinese","MISC"],["Liu Xiaobo","PER"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Liu","PER"],["China","LOC"],["Chinese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Serbia","LOC"],["Biden","PER"],["Belgrade","LOC"],["Serbia","LOC"],["JEREMIC","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["Washington","LOC"],["Balkans","LOC"],["Serbian","MISC"],["European Union","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["American","MISC"],["JEREMIC","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["International Herald Tribune","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["##ILLAR","ORG"],["RODHAM","ORG"],["##LIN","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Congress","ORG"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Conference on Population and Development I","MISC"],["##CP","ORG"],["##D","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin","LOC"],["Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United","MISC"],["Nations","ORG"],["International Conference on Population and Development","MISC"],["Cairo","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["ICPD","MISC"],["UN","ORG"],["Millennium Development Goals","MISC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Schl","ORG"],["##ter Bureau of Population Refugees and Migration U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","MISC"],["S. - Israel","MISC"],["Joint Economic Development Group","ORG"],["J","MISC"],["##ED","ORG"],["##G","MISC"],["Mid Year Review","MISC"],["Jerusalem","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Andy Baukol","PER"],["Treasury","ORG"],["Tom Engle","PER"],["Office of Monetary Affairs","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Stanley Fischer","PER"],["Bank of Israel","ORG"],["Chaim Shani","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Ministry of Finance","ORG"],["Eugene Kandel","PER"],["Israeli National Economic Council","ORG"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["##rae","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Year","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Jerusalem","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 15, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["United Nations Human Rights Council","ORG"],["Universal Periodic Review UPR","MISC"],["UP","MISC"],["UN","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["UN Human Rights Council","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Universal Periodic Review","MISC"],["Human Rights Council","ORG"],["Council","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["UP","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["Kyaw Zaw Lwin","PER"],["USG","ORG"],["Kyaw Zaw Lwin","PER"],["Kyaw Zaw Lwin","PER"],["Burmese","MISC"],["Kyaw Zaw Lwin","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Abkhazia","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S.","LOC"],["Nepal","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Nepal","LOC"],["United Communist Party of Nepal","ORG"],["Nepal","LOC"],["Nepali","MISC"],["Nepal","LOC"],["Nepal","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["Federal Register","ORG"],["Machine Read","MISC"],["Visa","MISC"],["Border Crossing Card","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Mexico","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["Georgetown","ORG"],["Gaston Hall","LOC"],["Jas","PER"],["Foreign Service School","ORG"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["DeGioia","PER"],["DeGioia","PER"],["Carol Lancaster","PER"],["School of Foreign Service","ORG"],["Human Rights Institute","ORG"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Amnesty International","ORG"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Obama","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Khartoum","LOC"],["Juba Sudan Stuttgart Germany","LOC"],["Brussels Belgium","LOC"],["Gration","PER"],["Khartoum","LOC"],["Juba Sudan","LOC"],["National Congress Party NCP","ORG"],["Sudan People ' s Liberation Movement","ORG"],["Stuttgart","LOC"],["Gration","PER"],["AFRICOM","ORG"],["Brussels","LOC"],["Gration","PER"],["European Union","ORG"],["Troika","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 14, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["John Bass","PER"],["Georgian","MISC"],["Nodar Kharshiladze","PER"],["##hida Kartli","LOC"],["Lado Vardzelashvili","PER"],["HALO Trust","ORG"],["Mghvrekisi","LOC"],["Gori District","LOC"],["##hida Kartli","LOC"],["Russia","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["HALO","ORG"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Shida Kartli","LOC"],["HALO","ORG"],["ER","MISC"],["HALO","ORG"],["##hida kartli","LOC"],["Bass","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Office of","ORG"],["Weapons","MISC"],["Removal and","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["clint","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["P","PER"],["J. Crowley","PER"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Valenzuela","PER"],["Ed Romero","PER"],["Ed","PER"],["OAS","ORG"],["Carmen Lomellin","PER"],["Carmen","PER"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["New York City San Antonio Texas","LOC"],["Miami Florida","LOC"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Georgetown University","ORG"],["Gaston Hall","LOC"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Edmund","LOC"],["A","ORG"],[".","LOC"],["Walsh","ORG"],["School","LOC"],["of Foreign Service","ORG"],["John J. DeGioia","PER"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Georgetown University Gaston","ORG"],["Hall","LOC"],["Healy Hall","LOC"],["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Rob Mathis","PER"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense or Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Rob Math","PER"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Democratic Society Party","ORG"],["Turkish Constitutional Court","ORG"],["Constitutional Court","ORG"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkish","MISC"],["Turkey","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 11, 2009","entities":[["Ellen Tauscher","PER"],["Polish","MISC"],["Defense","ORG"],["Stanislaw Komorowski","PER"],["Agreement","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Republic of Poland","LOC"],["Armed Forces of","ORG"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Republic of Poland","LOC"],["Warsaw","LOC"],["NATO Status of Forces Agreement","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Poland","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Missile Defense","MISC"],["##O","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["Poland","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["Arturo A. Valenzuela","PER"],["Brazil Argentina Uruguay","LOC"],["Paraguay","LOC"],["South America","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["R","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["##inian","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Afghanistan Pakistan","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Government Accountability Office","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["madaga","LOC"],["African Growth and Opportunity Act","MISC"],["Madagascar","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Malagasy","MISC"],["Transitional Government Cabinet","ORG"],["National Reconciliation Council","ORG"],["Independent Electoral Commission","ORG"],["Madagascar","LOC"],["AGOA","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["Madagascar","LOC"],["Madagascar","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 10, 2009","entities":[["Skies","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Japan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Japanese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["clint","PER"],["Martinez","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["Funes","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["martinez","PER"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Funes","PER"],["Funes","PER"],["Obama","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Poroshenko","PER"],["U","ORG"],["S.","MISC"],["- Ukraine Strategic Partnership Commission","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Lobo","PER"],["Arias","PER"],["Costa Rica","LOC"],["Martinelli","PER"],["Panama","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Inter American Democratic Charter","MISC"],["OAS","ORG"],["Arias","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["San Jose","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["Arias","PER"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Lobo","PER"],["Lo","LOC"],["Te","LOC"],["Hon","LOC"],["##ran","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Ukraine","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United Nations Universal Declaration of Human Rights","MISC"],["Universal Declaration","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Universal Declaration","MISC"],["International Human Rights Day","MISC"],["Eleanor Roosevelt","PER"],["Universal Declaration","MISC"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Human Rights Defenders Award","MISC"],["Maksharip Aushev","PER"],["Russia","LOC"],["Maksharip Aushev","PER"],["Russia","LOC"],["North Caucasus","LOC"],["Rights","MISC"],["Marie Yovan","PER"],["U","PER"],["U","LOC"],["Yovanov","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["B","MISC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["International Anti Corruption Day","MISC"],["Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development OECD","ORG"],["O","MISC"],["##EC","ORG"],["##D Anti Bribery Convention","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Gary Locke","PER"],["OECD","ORG"],["Angel Gurria","PER"],["International Anti Corruption Day","MISC"],["United Nations Convention against Corruption","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["Qatar","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["N","ORG"],["Convention","MISC"],["OECD","ORG"],["Anti Bribery Convention","MISC"],["Anti Bribery Convention","MISC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["N","ORG"],["OECD","ORG"],["Convention","MISC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["TOMS","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Voila Communication cell","ORG"],["##ire d '","ORG"],["##iti","ORG"],["ACE","MISC"],["u","MISC"],["s","MISC"],["TOMS","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S.","LOC"],["Voila Communication Cellulaire d ' Haiti","ORG"],["Trilogy International Partners","ORG"],["Haitian","MISC"],["Chevron Corporation","ORG"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Cisco Systems","ORG"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Cummins","ORG"],["China","LOC"],["Intel Corporation","ORG"],["Costa Rica","LOC"],["Marriott International","ORG"],["Jordan","LOC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Oracle Corporation","ORG"],["Romania","LOC"],["Protec","ORG"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["White am","ORG"],["Case LLP","ORG"],["Russia","LOC"],["ACE","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["##lint","PER"],["Benjamin","PER"],["Franklin","ORG"],["Room","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Ben Franklin","PER"],["2009 Awards for Corporate Excellence","MISC"],["ACE Awards","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Hormats","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Gary Locke","PER"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Dave Nelson","PER"],["Santa Monica","PER"],["California","LOC"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Martinez","PER"],["Buenos Aires","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["Africa","LOC"],["Memorandum on Trans","MISC"],["Open Government","MISC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Open Government Initiative","MISC"],["Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 9, 2009","entities":[["United Nations","ORG"],["Climate Change Conference","MISC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["White House","LOC"],["East Anglia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["Iraq","LOC"],["Baghdad","LOC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Iraqi","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["##lint","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Tony Blair","PER"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Mitchell","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["clint","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["FSO","ORG"],["FSO","ORG"],["FSO","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["de Tocqueville","PER"],["American","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 8, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Sudanese","MISC"],["Omdurman Sudan","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudanese","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Interim National Constitution","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Comprehensive Peace Agreement","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["Evo Morales","PER"],["Bolivian","MISC"],["Morales","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Bolivia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["Annual Conference of the","MISC"],["Parties","ORG"],["United","MISC"],["Nations","ORG"],["Framework Convention on Climate Change","MISC"],["UNFCCC","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["Center","ORG"],["National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration","ORG"],["NOAA","ORG"],["Earth","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["NOAA","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["S","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["Alexander Sandy MacDonald","PER"],["NOAA","ORG"],["Earth System Research Laboratory ESRL","ORG"],["Boulder Colorado","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["S","MISC"],["##C","MISC"],["Discovery Science Center","ORG"],["Santa Ana","LOC"],["CA","LOC"],["Museum of Science and Industry Chicago","ORG"],["IL","LOC"],["Boonshoft Museum of Discovery","ORG"],["Dayton","LOC"],["OH","LOC"],["Maryland Science Center","ORG"],["Baltimore","LOC"],["MD","LOC"],["Parker CO","ORG"],["Alaska State Museum","ORG"],["AK Science Museum","ORG"],["Minnesota","ORG"],["St","LOC"],["Paul","LOC"],["M","LOC"],["##N","LOC"],["James Madison University Harrisonburg","ORG"],["VA","LOC"],["Fiske Planetarium","ORG"],["Boulder CO","LOC"],["Heureka","ORG"],["Finnish Science Center Van","ORG"],["##taa Finland","LOC"],["NOAA ESRL Boulder CO","ORG"],["MacDonald","PER"],["Earth","LOC"],["Earth","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["##C","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Center","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Center","ORG"],["Sphere","ORG"],["NOAA NASA","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Energy","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["##C","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Center","ORG"],["Facebook","ORG"],["SphereC","ORG"],["NOAA","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["Nancy Lindberg","PER"],["Bill Lane","PER"],["James Bell","PER"],["Richard Stearns","PER"],["Liz Shrayer","PER"],["Andrea Mitchell","PER"],["Americans","MISC"],["Andrea","PER"],["Asia","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S. Global Leadership Coalition","ORG"],["US","LOC"],["USA","LOC"],["##ID","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Associates of the American Foreign Service Worldwide","ORG"],["Benjamin Franklin","LOC"],["Re","LOC"],["Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Associates of the American Foreign Service Worldwide","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["Erin P. Sweeney","PER"],["Lagos Nigeria Africa","LOC"],["JanMarie Flattum Riemers","PER"],["Jakarta Indonesia East Asia","LOC"],["Pacific","LOC"],["Lara L. Center","ORG"],["Luxembourg Europe","LOC"],["Joseph A. Taylor","PER"],["Baghdad Iraq Near East","LOC"],["South East Asia","LOC"],["Bernadetta J","PER"],["Ruch","PER"],["Dushanbe Tajikistan South Central Asia","LOC"],["Irene Miller","PER"],["Panama City Panama Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Brenda Greenberg","PER"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 7, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["PEPFAR Five Year Strategy","MISC"],["Global Con","MISC"],["of HIV","MISC"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["Global Health Initiative","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["Five Year","MISC"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["##EPFAR","ORG"],["Global Con","MISC"],["HIV","MISC"],["America","LOC"],["##EPFAR","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["Global","MISC"],["Health Initiative","ORG"],["Global Health Initiative","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Global Health Initiative","MISC"],["##EPFA","ORG"],["Year","MISC"],["Year","MISC"],["George W","PER"],["Bush","PER"],["PEPFAR","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 5, 2009","entities":[["Kennedy Center Honors","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin Room","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["##cumenical","MISC"],["Orthodox Church","ORG"],["Boss","PER"],["HBO","ORG"],["Carol Burnett","PER"],["Kennedy Center Honors","MISC"],["Ted Kennedy","PER"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Vicki Kennedy","PER"],["Jean Smith","PER"],["Caroline Kennedy","PER"],["Ted","PER"],["Kennedy Center","LOC"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Cold War","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Dave Brubeck","PER"],["American","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Berlin Wall","LOC"],["Velvet Revolution","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Berlin Wall","LOC"],["Bruce","PER"],["East Berlin","LOC"],["##ina","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["ESF","ORG"],["McC","PER"],["##tal","PER"],["British","MISC"],["British","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["US","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Re","LOC"],["Room","LOC"],["Magazine Publishers of America","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Magazine Publishers of America","ORG"],["Blair House","LOC"],["Re","LOC"],["Room","LOC"],["Better Homes and Gardens Martha Stewart Living Mother Earth News Natural Home","ORG"],["Old House","LOC"],["Traditional Home","LOC"],["Blair House","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["c","PER"],["NE","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin","ORG"],["NW Washington","LOC"],["C Street En","LOC"],["##nce","LOC"],["Press","ORG"],["Office","ORG"],["Press","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["West Point","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Arabic Dari English Pashto","MISC"],["Urdu","MISC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["English Dari","MISC"],["##ash","LOC"],["Urdu","MISC"],["Arabic English","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Arabic","MISC"],["##AF","ORG"],["Dar","LOC"],["##i","MISC"],["English","MISC"],["##AF","ORG"],["##AF","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["##ghanistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Latin America","LOC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Brief","MISC"],["Series","MISC"],["George C. Marshall Conference Center","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["21st Street","LOC"],["21st Street","LOC"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["Press Brief","ORG"],["Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["RS","ORG"],["Press","ORG"],["B","LOC"],["##rief","ORG"],["Room","LOC"],["Office of Regional Media Outreach","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of state","ORG"],["Yvonne Ribeiro","PER"],["Yemofio","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Colin L. Powell","PER"],["Ben Franklin Room","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Ben Franklin Room","LOC"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Janine Zachria","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Erdogan","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iraq Middle East","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Erdogan","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Europe","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Iran Iraq Afghanistan Pakistan Middle East Greece","LOC"],["European Union","ORG"],["Erdogan","PER"],["Turkey","LOC"],["E","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Turkey","LOC"],["Armenia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Mogadishu","LOC"],["Transitional Federal Government","ORG"],["Somali","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Somali","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["A S Blake","PER"],["Sri Lanka","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Treaty on the Reduction and Limitation of Strategic Offensive Arms","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Belarus","LOC"],["Republic of Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Union of Soviet Socialist Republics","LOC"],["Reduction","MISC"],["Limitation of Strategic Offensive Arms","MISC"],["START Treaty","MISC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Belarus","LOC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["N","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Belarus","LOC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Ukraine","LOC"],["Protocol to the START Treaty","MISC"],["N","MISC"],["Budapest Me","MISC"],["##anda","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["Russian Federation","LOC"],["Budapest Me","MISC"],["##anda","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 4, 2009","entities":[["Ten","MISC"],["Meeting","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S.","MISC"],["Mexico","LOC"],["High Level Consultative Commission on Telecommunications HLCC","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["Philip L","PER"],["Verveer","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["International Communications and Information Policy","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["gab","PER"],["##a her","PER"],["##dez card","PER"],["Mexican","MISC"],["Ministry of Communications and Transportation","ORG"],["G. Osuna Jaime","PER"],["Mexico","LOC"],["Federal Telecommunications Commission","ORG"],["National Public Safety Telecommunications Council","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Advisory Committee on International Communications and Information Policy","ORG"],["HLCC","ORG"],["Mexico","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["HLCC","ORG"],["Directory","MISC"],["B","MISC"],["William H","PER"],["ha","PER"],["##rig","PER"],["Communications and Information","ORG"],["Office of Bila","ORG"],["and","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Kerry","PER"],["Lugar","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Congress","ORG"],["Committee","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["West Point","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["York","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["##lint","PER"],["clint","PER"],["clint","PER"],["##lint","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["Holbrooke","PER"],["Jim Steinberg","PER"],["Phil Gordon","PER"],["Ivo Daalder","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["Rasmussen","PER"],["##lint","PER"],["Gates","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Ian Kelly","PER"],["KELLY","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Ian Kelly","PER"],["Valenzuel","PER"],["##a ASSIST","ORG"],["##alenzuel","PER"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Manuel Zelaya","PER"],["Honduran","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Micheletti","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Lew","PER"],["Hill","LOC"],["House Armed Services Committee","ORG"],["Brussels","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["North Atlantic Council","ORG"],["NATO Russia Council","ORG"],["ISAF","ORG"],["ISAF","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["Rasmussen","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["Gates","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Mullen","PER"],["Hill","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Ka","PER"],["Mu","PER"],["Omar","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["for Justice Federal Bureau of Investigation","ORG"],["Pan Am Flight 73","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"],["Wadoud Muhammad Hafiz al Turki Jamal Saeed Abdul Rahim Muhammad Abdullah Khalil Hussain ar rahayyal","PER"],["Muhammad Ahmed al Munawar","PER"],["Abu","PER"],["Ni","ORG"],["##dal","PER"],["District of Columbia","LOC"],["Pan American World Airways","ORG"],["Flight 73","MISC"],["Karachi Pakistan","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Federal Bureau of Investigation","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S.","LOC"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Wadoud Muhammad Hafiz al Turki","PER"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Wadoud Muhammad Fahd al Turk Sliman Ali Ahmad El Turk","PER"],["Salman Ali El Turk","PER"],["Bou Baker Muhammad Sulaiman Alturki","PER"],["Sulai","PER"],["Tu","PER"],["Jamal Saeed Abdul Rahim","PER"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Ali Al Jass","PER"],["F","PER"],["F","PER"],["Ali al J","PER"],["Jamal Saeed Abdul","PER"],["##im F","PER"],["Ali Al J","PER"],["Isma","PER"],["F","PER"],["##ad Muhammad Abdullah K","PER"],["Hussain","PER"],["##ayyal","PER"],["Lebanon","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["s","LOC"],["Grand H","LOC"],["##yatt","ORG"],["USGLC","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["America","LOC"],["NBC News","ORG"],["Andrea Mitchell","PER"],["James Bell","PER"],["Boeing Company","ORG"],["Richard Stearns","PER"],["World Vision","ORG"],["##ton","ORG"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Richard parkerus Global Leadership Coalition","ORG"],["Press RelationsU.","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["American Pakistan Foundation","ORG"],["Cipriani","LOC"],["New York City","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Pakistani American","MISC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Colin Powell","PER"],["USA","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["##en Qureshi","PER"],["Foundation","ORG"],["Pakistani","MISC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["American Pakistan Foundation","ORG"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["American Pakistan Foundation","ORG"],["americanpakistan","ORG"],["##ericanpakistan","ORG"],["East 42nd StreetNew York City","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Lynne Tracy","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Tracy","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Peshawar Pakistan","LOC"],["Peshawar","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Lynne Tracy","PER"],["South","MISC"],["Central Asian","MISC"],["AffairsU. S. Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Press RelationsU. S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["B","MISC"],["##C","ORG"],["##F","ORG"],["##R","ORG"],["##stan","LOC"],["##e Tracy","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Peshawar Pakistan","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Tracy","PER"],["Central","LOC"],["South Asia","LOC"],["As","LOC"],["Kabul","LOC"],["Washington","LOC"],["Kazakhstan","LOC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Office","ORG"],["States","LOC"],["Tracy","PER"],["Ohio","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["Georgia","LOC"],["Akron","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["Tim Padgett","PER"],["Time Magazine","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["##NI","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Santos","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Arturo","PER"],["Vale","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["ADMI","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 3, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"],["Istvan Serto Radics","PER"],["Serto Radics","PER"],["Hungarian","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Hubert H. Humphrey Fellowship","MISC"],["Fulbright Visiting Scholar","MISC"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["Office of Alumni Affairs","ORG"],["Serto Radics","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Johns Hopkins University","ORG"],["Humphrey","PER"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Uszka","LOC"],["Roma","MISC"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Uszka","LOC"],["Roma","MISC"],["Serto Radic","PER"],["Uszka","LOC"],["European Union","ORG"],["United States Democracy","MISC"],["and Civil Society","ORG"],["Award","MISC"],["Roma","MISC"],["Serto Radics","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["University of Mississippi","ORG"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Serto Radics","PER"],["Mississippi","LOC"],["Hungary","LOC"],["Hungary","LOC"],["European Union","ORG"],["Hungarian","MISC"],["Committee","ORG"],["European Union","ORG"],["Commission","ORG"],["Relations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["Educational","ORG"],["Catherine","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 2, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["International Day for","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 2, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Awards for","MISC"],["Excellence","MISC"],["Benjamin Franklin Room","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["ACE","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["ACE","MISC"],["ACE","MISC"],["Chevron Corporation","ORG"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Cisco Systems","ORG"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Cummins China Intel Corporation","ORG"],["Costa Rica","LOC"],["Marriott International","ORG"],["Jordan","LOC"],["Officenet Staples","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["Oracle Corporation","ORG"],["Romania","LOC"],["Protec","ORG"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["TOMS","ORG"],["Argentina","LOC"],["White Case LLP","ORG"],["Russia","LOC"],["Robert D. Hormats","PER"],["Energy and Agricultural Affairs","ORG"],["ACE","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Kerry Humphrey","PER"],["Bureau of Economic Energy and Business Affairs","ORG"],["Office of Press","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["Advisory Committee on Historical Diplomatic Documentation","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["National Archives and Records Administration","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Margaret Morris","PER"],["##sey Office of the Historian","ORG"],["US","LOC"],["Margaret Morrissey","PER"],["Edward Brynn","PER"],["Advisory Committee on Historical Diplomatic Documentation Department of State Office of the Historian","ORG"],["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Brussels","LOC"],["North Atlantic Council NAC","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["Headquarters","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Non","MISC"],["NATO","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["##uss","MISC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Rasmussen","PER"],["Belgian","MISC"],["Yves Leterme","PER"],["Steven Vanackere","PER"],["EU","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["Eric Goosby","PER"],["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["AIDS","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Tu","MISC"],["##losis","MISC"],["Malaria","MISC"],["Goosby","PER"],["GO","PER"],["##OS","ORG"],["PEP","MISC"],["##R","MISC"],["State Department USAID CDC Department of Defense Peace Corps","ORG"],["Bush","PER"],["Congress","ORG"],["PEP","MISC"],["##R","MISC"],["African","MISC"],["P","ORG"],["##EP","MISC"],["##R","ORG"],["##EPFAR","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Kenya","LOC"],["Committee of Experts","ORG"],["Kenya","LOC"],["Kenya","LOC"],["Kenyan","MISC"],["Kenyan","MISC"],["Kibaki","PER"],["Odinga","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Kenyan","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Tu","MISC"],["##losis","MISC"],["Malaria","MISC"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["US","MISC"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["TB","MISC"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["US","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["World AIDS Day","MISC"],["Five Year","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["##EPFAR","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["Global","MISC"],["Health Initiative PEPFAR","ORG"],["Year","MISC"],["George W","PER"],["Bush","PER"],["##FA","ORG"],["PEPFAR","ORG"],["##EPFA","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Cartagena","LOC"],["Second Review Conference","MISC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Pro","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Review Conference","MISC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Ottawa","MISC"],["Uribe","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Administration","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Amended Mines Protocol","MISC"],["Convention on Certain Conventional Weapons","MISC"],["Administration","ORG"],["Review Conference","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Emirati","MISC"],["United Arab Emirates","LOC"],["38th National Day","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Cairo","LOC"],["UAE","LOC"],["UAE","LOC"],["Zayed Bin Sultan Al Nahyan","PER"],["Khalifa Bin Zayed Al Nahyan","PER"],["Mohammed Bin Rashid Al Maktoum","PER"],["Supreme Council of the Federation","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["UAE","LOC"],["Emirati","MISC"],["National Day","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"December 1, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Revolutionary Armed Forces of Colombia FARC","ORG"],["Second Review Conference","MISC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Cartagena Colombia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Colombian","MISC"],["Action Against","MISC"],["personnel Mines","MISC"],["Colombian","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Colombia Humanitarian Demining","MISC"],["Workshop","MISC"],["Bogota","LOC"],["Colombian","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Organization of American States","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Colombian","MISC"],["Centro Integral de Rehabilitacion de Colombia","ORG"],["Seeds of Hope","ORG"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Campaign to","ORG"],["Ban","MISC"],["Land","ORG"],["##mine","MISC"],["##s","ORG"],["The Polus Center","ORG"],["Colombian","MISC"],["Information Management and Mine Action Program","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S. Agency for International Development","ORG"],["Mercy Corps","ORG"],["Colombian","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Southern Command","ORG"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Office","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["KELL","ORG"],["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["West Hemisphere","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["##alenzuel","PER"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Pepe Lobo","PER"],["Ham","PER"],["Avila","PER"],["Martinez","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["Zelaya","PER"],["San Jose Accords","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["San","LOC"],["Jose","PER"],["Spanish","MISC"],["Hon","MISC"],["##ran","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["Jacob J","PER"],["Lew","PER"],["Eric Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["AIDS","MISC"],["World AIDS Day","MISC"],["The World Bank","ORG"],["Keeping the Promise","MISC"],["Future Link","MISC"],["HIV AIDS","MISC"],["Child Health","MISC"],["Lew","PER"],["Goosby","PER"],["Michel Kazatchkine","PER"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["Tu","MISC"],["##is","MISC"],["Malaria","MISC"],["Joy Phumaphi","PER"],["World Bank","ORG"],["Botswana","LOC"],["Julian Schweitzer","PER"],["Development","ORG"],["World Bank","ORG"],["The World Bank","ORG"],["World Bank","ORG"],["Preston Auditorium","LOC"],["St","LOC"],["N","LOC"],["W","LOC"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["RSVP","ORG"],["Jennifer Peterson","PER"],["u","LOC"],["s","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["##lint","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["Rudd","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Oval Office","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Australia","LOC"],["rudd","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Australia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["America","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["c","PER"],["rudd","PER"],["c","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Humanitarian Mine Action Program","ORG"],["Department of State Department of Defense","ORG"],["International Development","ORG"],["Centers for Disease Control and Prevention","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Humanitarian Mine Action Program","ORG"],["Costa Rica Djibouti Guatemala Honduras Kosovo Macedonia Namibia Rwanda","LOC"],["Suriname","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["Humanitarian Mine Action","MISC"],["Afghanistan Bosnia Colombia Iraq Laos","LOC"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Convention on Certain Conventional Weapons CCW","MISC"],["Am","MISC"],["Protocol II","MISC"],["Protocol V","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Organization of the Islamic Conference OIC","ORG"],["Eradicate Polio","MISC"],["UNICEF","ORG"],["New York City","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Cairo","LOC"],["OIC","ORG"],["UNICEF","ORG"],["Ann M. Veneman","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Economic and Social Council of","ORG"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Frederick D. Barton","PER"],["Observer Mission","ORG"],["Organization of the Islamic Conference","ORG"],["United Nations","ORG"],["New York","LOC"],["Abdul Wahab","PER"],["William Foege","PER"],["Melinda Gates Foundation","ORG"],["Bruce Aylward","PER"],["Global Pol","ORG"],["##io","MISC"],["Eradication Initiative","ORG"],["World Health Organization","ORG"],["Jim Lacy","PER"],["Rotary International","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Raza Tarar","PER"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Erin Mc","PER"],["##L","ORG"],["##inn","PER"],["Bureau of International Organization Affairs Office of Public Affairs and Outreach","ORG"],["Office of Press Relations U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 30, 2009","entities":[["Mujica","PER"],["Uruguay","LOC"],["Uruguay","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Mujica","PER"],["Uruguay","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 29, 2009","entities":[["Honduran","MISC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Americas","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["sa","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["Ian Kelly","PER"],["Ian Kelly","PER"],["IAEA","ORG"],["Vienna","LOC"],["International Atomic Energy Agency Board of Governors","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["IAEA","ORG"],["UN Security Council","ORG"],["IAEA","ORG"],["NPT","ORG"],["Mohamed ElBaradei","PER"],["IAEA","ORG"],["Tehran","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Russia China France Germany","LOC"],["Britain","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Russia China","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Board","ORG"],["Jones","PER"],["NSC","ORG"],["Vienna","LOC"],["Board","ORG"],["Mohamed El","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Barbados","LOC"],["United States","ORG"],["##ar Agency","ORG"],["Bridgetown","LOC"],["Eastern Caribbean","LOC"],["Barbados","LOC"],["Barbados","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Organization of American States","ORG"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["Zelaya","PER"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Supreme Electoral Tribunal","ORG"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"],["Honduras","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"],["Tegucigalpa","LOC"],["Honduran","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 27, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Khartoum Abyei","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Khartoum","LOC"],["Comprehensive Peace Agreement","MISC"],["CPA","ORG"],["National Congress Party NCP","ORG"],["Sudan People ' s Liberation Movement","ORG"],["Southern Sudan","LOC"],["Abyei","LOC"],["Gration","PER"],["Abyei","LOC"],["Permanent Court of Arbitration","ORG"],["PCA","ORG"],["Darfur","LOC"],["##ration","PER"],["Chad","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Khartoum Abyei","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Sudanese","MISC"],["Sudanese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 26, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Sahrawi","MISC"],["Aminatou Haidar","PER"],["Robert F. Kennedy","MISC"],["Train Foundation","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["Mitchell","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Mitchell","PER"],["MITCHELL","ORG"],["Netanyahu","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Arab States","LOC"],["Palestinians","MISC"],["Arab","MISC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Israel","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["West Bank","LOC"],["Israeli","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["Arabic","MISC"],["Hebrew","MISC"],["##rael","ORG"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Palestinian","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"],["Jewish","MISC"],["Israeli","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["HIV AIDS","MISC"],["Health and Human Services","ORG"],["Kathleen Sebelius","PER"],["Eric P. Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Valerie Jarrett","PER"],["State Department Press Corp","ORG"],["White House","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Social Security","MISC"],["Obama","MISC"],["Administration","ORG"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Health and Human Services","ORG"],["Kathleen Sebelius","PER"],["Eric P. Goosby","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Valerie Jarrett","PER"],["Jeffrey S. Crowley","PER"],["White House Office of National AIDS Policy","ORG"],["Eisenhower Executive Office Building","LOC"],["Eisenhower Executive Office Building","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["India","LOC"],["Singh","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Article","MISC"],["U","MISC"],["S. - India Nuclear Cooperation Agreement","MISC"],["Singh","PER"],["U","MISC"],["S. - India Civil Nuclear Cooperation Initiative","MISC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["White House","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["UN Framework Convention on Climate Change","MISC"],["Copenhagen Denmark","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["Bella Conference Center","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Earth","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S. Center","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Federal","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Copenhagen","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 25, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Elimination of Violence Against Women Day","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Melanne Verveer","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Democratic","MISC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Congo","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["Nations","ORG"],["Council","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["Department of State Advisory Committee","ORG"],["International Law","ORG"],["George Washington University Law","ORG"],["School Michael K. Young","LOC"],["Faculty Conference","ORG"],["Center","LOC"],["St","LOC"],["NW Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Harold H","PER"],["Koh","PER"],["International Criminal Court","ORG"],["International Court of Justice","ORG"],["mexican","MISC"],["Mexico","LOC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Office of the Legal Adviser","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Cote d ' Ivoire","LOC"],["cote d ' ivoire","LOC"],["Cote d ' Ivoire","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Cote d ' Ivoire","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["Bob","PER"],["Krishna","PER"],["Ahluwalia","PER"],["India","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Copenhagen","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["India","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["State Department","ORG"],["Kaur","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["Joe Biden","PER"],["Jill Biden","PER"],["United States Senate","ORG"],["India","LOC"],["Friends of India Caucus","ORG"],["Senate","ORG"],["Biden","PER"],["Senate Foreign Relations Committee","ORG"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["India","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Singh","PER"],["India","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Krishna","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["For Justice Federal Bureau of Investigation","ORG"],["Husayn Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Husayn Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["Abu Ibrahim Husayn Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["FBI","ORG"],["Pan American World Airways","ORG"],["Al Umari","PER"],["Narita Japan","LOC"],["Honolulu Hawaii","LOC"],["Al Umari","PER"],["District of Columbia","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. District Court","ORG"],["Mohammad Rashed","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["al Umari","PER"],["France","LOC"],["Marks and Spencer Department","ORG"],["Paris","LOC"],["Leumi Bank","ORG"],["Al Umari","PER"],["Jaffa","LOC"],["British","MISC"],["Palestine","LOC"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Lebanon","LOC"],["Iraq","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["##GB","ORG"],["German","MISC"],["Army","ORG"],["Irish Republican","MISC"],["Army","ORG"],["Basque","MISC"],["Liberty","ORG"],["Japanese","MISC"],["Army","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S. Department of State","ORG"],["Husayn Muhammed al Umari","PER"],["Abu Ibrahim","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Second Review Conference","MISC"],["1997 Convention on the Prohibition","MISC"],["Ottawa Convention","MISC"],["Cartagena Colombia","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Party","MISC"],["Convention","MISC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 24, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S.","MISC"],["South African","MISC"],["Pretoria South Africa","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Programs","MISC"],["Bonnie Jenkins","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S.","MISC"],["South Africa","LOC"],["Non","MISC"],["Di","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Robert Einhorn","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S.","MISC"],["South Africa","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 23, 2009","entities":[["Bulgarian","MISC"],["Zheleva","PER"],["Europe","LOC"],["Euro Atlantic","MISC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Central","LOC"],["Eastern Europe","LOC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Bulgarian","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["European Union","ORG"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Eurasian","MISC"],["Richard Morningstar","PER"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Bulgarian","MISC"],["Clinton","PER"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 23, 2009","entities":[["KELL","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["KELL","ORG"],["Dombey","PER"],["KELL","ORG"],["Wood","PER"],["KELL","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["KELL","ORG"],["Robert","PER"],["Kabul","LOC"],["KELL","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"],["KELL","ORG"],["Brussels","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["IAEA","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Board","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Council","ORG"],["Board","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 23, 2009","entities":[["Department of State","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Asia","LOC"],["Kabul","LOC"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Richard Holbrooke","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Richard","PER"],["Richard","PER"],["##OL","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Dereck Hogan","PER"],["State Department Foreign Service","ORG"],["Maureen White","PER"],["Department","ORG"],["Treasury","ORG"],["Beth","PER"],["Julie","PER"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["USA","LOC"],["##ID","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["Michele Bond","PER"],["Directorate for Overseas Citizens Services","ORG"],["Office of Policy Coordination and Public Outreach","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Bureau of Consular Affairs","ORG"],["Office of Overseas Citizens Services","ORG"],["Bond","PER"],["Overseas Citizens Services","ORG"],["Bureau of Consular Affairs","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["The Hague Convention on Inter Country Adoption","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["State Department","ORG"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Hague","LOC"],["Convention","MISC"],["Country","MISC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["Micheletti","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["U","MISC"],["S.","MISC"],["Brazil","MISC"],["Joint Commission","ORG"],["Meeting","MISC"],["John Holdren","PER"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["White House Office of Science and Technology Policy","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Sergio Rezende","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Ministry for Science and Technology","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Nina Fedoroff","PER"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Agency for International Development","ORG"],["John Holdren","PER"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Rezende","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["u","MISC"],["s.","MISC"],["brazilian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Agency for International Development","ORG"],["Brazilian Agency for International Cooperation","ORG"],["Brazilian Agricultural Research Corporation","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Joint","MISC"],["Commission","ORG"],["Meeting","MISC"],["Patrick Gallagher","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["National Institute of Standards and Technology","ORG"],["Joao Alziro herz da","PER"],["Jornada","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["National Institute of Metro","ORG"],["Ministry","ORG"],["Industry","ORG"],["Foreign","ORG"],["Richard Wyatt","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["National Institutes","ORG"],["Health","ORG"],["F","ORG"],["Center","ORG"],["Jorge","ORG"],["##da G","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Federal Agency","ORG"],["Education Foundation","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 20, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["i","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iranian","MISC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["UN","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Working Group","ORG"],["Iran","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["McChrystal","PER"],["rodriguez","PER"],["NATO","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Administration","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Ka","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Jack Lew","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Afghanistan Camp Atterbury Musca","LOC"],["##tat","MISC"],["##uck Center","ORG"],["CA MCCO","ORG"],["Indiana","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["NATO","MISC"],["International Security Assistance Force ISAF","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["CA MCC","ORG"],["State Department USAID","ORG"],["Department of State USAID","ORG"],["Department of Agriculture","ORG"],["Afghan","MISC"],["CA MCCO","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Yemeni","MISC"],["Guantanamo Detention Facility","LOC"],["Yemeni","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Afghanistan","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Hamid Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Karzai","PER"],["Ka","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Hamid Karzai","PER"],["British","MISC"],["clint","PER"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Karzai","PER"],["Karzai","PER"],["clint","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Hamid Ka","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Clinton","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Radio Azadi","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Hamid Karzai","PER"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Taliban","ORG"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Taliban","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["Taliban","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Van Rompuy","PER"],["Ashton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iranian","MISC"],["Middle East","LOC"],["Javier Solana","PER"],["Benita Ferrero Waldner","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["c","PER"],["Eikenberry","PER"],["McChrystal","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["NATO","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Eikenberry","PER"],["McChrystal","PER"],["Holbrooke","PER"],["Washington","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["USA","LOC"],["##ID","ORG"],["Kabul","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Canada","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Canada","LOC"],["Air Quality Agreement","MISC"],["Government of","ORG"],["Canada","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Bagram","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Republic","LOC"],["Suriname","LOC"],["Americas","LOC"],["suriname","LOC"],["Suriname Independence Day Marathon","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["South Dakota","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["suriname","MISC"],["##kot","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 19, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Khartoum Abyei","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Gration","PER"],["Abyei","LOC"],["Permanent Court of Arbitration","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Black Consciousness Day","MISC"],["Zumbi dos palmares","MISC"],["Quil","MISC"],["##omb","PER"],["Zumbi","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Afro","MISC"],["Salvador da Bahia","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Afro","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Hemisphere","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["Karzai","PER"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["Overseas Security Advisory Council","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["eiken","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Afghan","MISC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Eikenberry","PER"],["Eikenberry","PER"],["Frank","PER"],["Marie","PER"],["Tony","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["Clinton","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Karzai","PER"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["US","MISC"],["Provincial Reconstruction Teams","ORG"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Serbian Orthodox","MISC"],["Church","ORG"],["p","PER"],["Serbian Orthodox","MISC"],["Church","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 18, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["U","MISC"],["S. - Brazil Joint","MISC"],["Commission","ORG"],["Meeting on Science","MISC"],["and Technology","ORG"],["Cooperation","MISC"],["Loy Henderson Auditorium","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["John Holdren","PER"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["White House","LOC"],["Office of Science and Technology Policy","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Sergio Rezende","PER"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["Ministry for Science and Technology","ORG"],["Brazilian","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Joint Commission Meeting","MISC"],["Nina Fedoroff","PER"],["Science and Technology","ORG"],["Rezende","PER"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Holdren","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["Department of State White House Congress Department of Defense","ORG"],["Foreign Press Center","ORG"],["Alice Chu","PER"],["Department of State Bureau","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Hillary Rodham Clinton","PER"],["Department of State","ORG"],["ExchangesC","MISC"],["##on","ORG"],["##nect","MISC"],["Contest Change Your Climate Change Our World","MISC"],["ExchangesConnect","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs ECA","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["ExchangesConnect","ORG"],["ExchangesConnect","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["ExchangesConnect","ORG"],["ExchangesConnect","ORG"],["ECA","ORG"],["Jay Craven","PER"],["AFI","ORG"],["Global Cultural Exchange Program","ORG"],["Vassilios Karamitsanis","PER"],["Platforma International Film Festival","ORG"],["Urban Cultural Company","ORG"],["Josef Frank Madisia","PER"],["National Art Gallery Namibia International Visitor Leadership Program","ORG"],["Rodolfo Molina","PER"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Biennials of Visual Arts","MISC"],["Fulbright","MISC"],["Program","MISC"],["Hind Shoufani","PER"],["##bright","ORG"],["Department","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Office of Protocol","ORG"],["Office of the Chief of Protocol","ORG"],["White House","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Czechoslovakia","LOC"],["Polish","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Prague","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Czech Republic","LOC"],["Slovakia","LOC"],["Tomas Masaryk","PER"],["Middle Europe","LOC"],["Czech Republic","LOC"],["Slovakia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Ida","MISC"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["San Salvador","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Government","ORG"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Agency for International Development","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of Defense","ORG"],["Southern Command","ORG"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Armed Forces","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Miami","LOC"],["USAID","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Southern Command","ORG"],["Projects","MISC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Southern Command","ORG"],["Joint Task Force Bravo","ORG"],["Hon","ORG"],["##du","LOC"],["##ran Air Force","ORG"],["Base Soto","LOC"],["El Salvador","LOC"],["Salvador","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 17, 2009","entities":[["Greek","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S.","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Institute of International Education IIE","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["Judith A. McHale","PER"],["National Press Club","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["EducationUSA","ORG"],["##usa","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of Commerce","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["ECA","ORG"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Kosovo","LOC"],["Kosovo","LOC"],["Kosovo Serb","MISC"],["Kosovo","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Open Doors","ORG"],["Americans","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Institute of International Education","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["Judith A. McHale","PER"],["National Press Club","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["International Education Week","MISC"],["State Department","ORG"],["Fulbright Program","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["a","MISC"],["gilman International Scholarship Program","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Door","ORG"],["China Ireland Austria","LOC"],["India","LOC"],["Costa Rica Japan Argentina","LOC"],["South Africa","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["United Kingdom Italy Spain","LOC"],["France","LOC"],["Western Europe","LOC"],["English","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Africa","LOC"],["Asia","LOC"],["Latin America","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","MISC"],["Department","ORG"],["Bureau","ORG"],["EC","ORG"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Catherine St","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["Chinese","MISC"],["Ken Jarrett","PER"],["USA","LOC"],["Board of","ORG"],["Yang Xiong","PER"],["Zhong Yanq","PER"],["Hong Hao","PER"],["Wu","PER"],["Chinese","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Zhou Wenzhong","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Jose Villarreal","PER"],["Beatrice Camp","PER"],["Elizabeth Bagley","PER"],["Kris Balderston","PER"],["State Department","ORG"],["Ellen Eliasoph","PER"],["s","LOC"],["USA","LOC"],["PepsiCo General Electric Corporation","ORG"],["Chevron","ORG"],["Proctor and Gamble","ORG"],["Honeywell Intel Pfizer","ORG"],["Qualcomm","ORG"],["Boeing","ORG"],["American","MISC"],["USA","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["China","LOC"],["Shanghai","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["China","LOC"],["USA","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["America","LOC"],["USA","LOC"],["Expo","ORG"],["American","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Scott Gration","PER"],["Sudan","LOC"],["Khartoum Abyei South Sudan","LOC"],["Jebel Marra Darfur","LOC"],["Khartoum","LOC"],["Gration","PER"],["National Congress Party NCP","ORG"],["Sudan People ' s Liberation Movement","ORG"],["Comprehensive Peace Agreement","MISC"],["g","PER"],["Abyei","LOC"],["Permanent Court of Arbitration","ORG"],["Gration","PER"],["El Fasher","LOC"],["Jebel Marra","LOC"],["Darfur","LOC"],["Darfuri","MISC"],["Darfur","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 16, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Angola","LOC"],["Strategic Partnership Dialogue","MISC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Angola","LOC"],["Angolan","MISC"],["dos Anjos","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Angola","LOC"],["Strategic Partnership Dialogue","MISC"],["Security Cooperation","ORG"],["Donald Yamamoto","PER"],["Bureau of African Affairs","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Angolan","MISC"],["Josefina Pitra Diakite","PER"],["Energy Cooperation","ORG"],["David Goldwyn","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Angolan","MISC"],["Joao Baptista Borges","PER"],["Angola","LOC"],["Angolan","MISC"],["Woodrow Wilson Center","ORG"],["U","MISC"],["S. - Angola Day","MISC"],["Ronald Reagan International Trade Center","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["African","MISC"],["Johnnie Carson","PER"],["Earl Gast","PER"],["David Goldwyn","PER"],["Department of Energy","ORG"],["Department of Homeland Security","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["Justine Lindemann","PER"],["Justine","PER"],["Linde","PER"],["##mann","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 13, 2009","entities":[["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Office of Weapons Removal and Abatement","ORG"],["Bureau of Political Military Affairs","ORG"],["Budva Montenegro","LOC"],["South East Europe","LOC"],["South East","LOC"],["Europe Regional A","MISC"],["Defense Ministry and General Staff","ORG"],["South East European","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["of State","ORG"],["Defense","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S. European Command","ORG"],["Croatia","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Albania Bulgaria","LOC"],["Serbia","LOC"],["PM WRA","ORG"],["WRA","ORG"],["Bulgaria","LOC"],["Chelopechne","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["##tia","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 13, 2009","entities":[["James Lilley","PER"],["Jim","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["East Asia","LOC"],["American Institute","ORG"],["Taiwan","LOC"],["Jim","PER"],["Republic of Korea","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["China","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Tiananmen Incident","MISC"],["East Asia","LOC"],["Jim","PER"],["Foreign Service","ORG"],["Jim","PER"],["China","LOC"],["Confucian","MISC"],["American","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 13, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Hillary Clinton","PER"],["c","PER"],["Clinton","PER"],["Philippines","LOC"],["c","PER"],["Luzon Visayas","LOC"],["Mindanao","LOC"],["New York","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["c","PER"],["Maria","PER"],["United States","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["Bureau of Population Refugees and Migration","ORG"],["Eric P. Schwartz","PER"],["Iraq Jordan","LOC"],["Syria","LOC"],["Iraqi","MISC"],["Palestinian","MISC"],["United States","MISC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Jordan","LOC"],["Schwartz","PER"],["United Nations Relief and Works Agency","ORG"],["Near East","LOC"],["UNRWA","ORG"],["USG","MISC"],["UNRWA","ORG"],["UNRWA","ORG"],["Karen AbuZayd","PER"],["Beth Schlachter","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["Filipino Americans","MISC"],["American","MISC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["##IC","ORG"],["Mabuhay","ORG"],["Mabuhay","ORG"],["United States of America","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["God","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Union of Greek Shipowners","ORG"],["Andrew J","PER"],["Shapiro","PER"],["Thomas M","PER"],["Countryman","PER"],["Robert W","PER"],["Maggi","PER"],["Department","ORG"],["Somalia","LOC"],["Theodore Veniamis","PER"],["Michael Chandris Georgios Gratsos","PER"],["UGS Board","ORG"],["Hellenic Chamber of Shipping","ORG"],["John Lyras","PER"],["UGS Board","ORG"],["Anna Bred","PER"],["##ima UGS","ORG"],["EU","ORG"],["Department","ORG"],["Shapiro","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Greece","LOC"],["New York Declaration","MISC"],["International Maritime Organization","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Greece","LOC"],["Contact Group","ORG"],["Pi","MISC"],["Coast of Somalia","LOC"],["Contact Group","ORG"],["Contact Group","ORG"],["Somali","ORG"],["Washington","LOC"],["Department","ORG"],["Transportation Department","ORG"],["Homeland Security U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Coast Guard Federal Maritime Commission Military Seal","ORG"],["Command Environmental Protection Agency","ORG"],["House Subcommittee","ORG"],["Coast Guard","ORG"],["Maritime Transportation","ORG"],["Somalia","ORG"],["United States","ORG"],["##iracy","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["romulo","PER"],["Hillary Clinton","PER"],["Manila","LOC"],["Bill Clinton","PER"],["APEC","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Bataan","LOC"],["##dor","LOC"],["Ketsana","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S. Navy","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Romulo","PER"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Filipino","MISC"],["Obama","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["Richard Holbrooke","PER"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Paris","LOC"],["Munich","LOC"],["Moscow","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Pakistan","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["as","LOC"],["pacific","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["US","MISC"],["Asia Pacific","LOC"],["Philippines U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Philippine","MISC"],["Ketsana","MISC"],["Metropolitan Manila","LOC"],["USAID","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of Agriculture","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S. Department of Defense","ORG"],["Clinton","PER"],["Manila","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Indonesia","LOC"],["Padang West Sumatra","LOC"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of Defense","ORG"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["Vietnam","LOC"],["Ketsana","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["International Federation of the Red Cross","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["Mirinae","MISC"],["Laos","LOC"],["Sa","LOC"],["Province","MISC"],["Ke","MISC"],["Samoa","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Tonga USA","LOC"],["##ID","ORG"],["US","LOC"],["Asia Pacific","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["United Nations","ORG"],["Mandela International Day","MISC"],["Nelson Mandela","PER"],["Nelson Mandela","PER"],["South Africa","LOC"],["Mandela","PER"],["South Africa","LOC"],["F","PER"],["W. de Klerk","PER"],["Nobel Peace Prize","MISC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Nelson Mandela","PER"],["South Africa","LOC"],["Mandela International Day","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["General Assembly","ORG"],["Adop","MISC"],["Nelson Mandela International Day","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 12, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Angola","LOC"],["Strategic Partnership Dialogue","MISC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Angola","LOC"],["Angolan","MISC"],["dos Anjos","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Angola","LOC"],["Strategic Partnership Dialogue","MISC"],["Security Cooperation","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Donald Yamamoto","PER"],["Bureau of African Affairs","ORG"],["Energy Cooperation","ORG"],["Energy","ORG"],["David Goldwyn","PER"],["Angolan","MISC"],["Woodrow Wilson Center","ORG"],["U","MISC"],["S.","MISC"],["Angola Day","MISC"],["Ronald Reagan International Trade Center","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["African","MISC"],["Johnnie Carson","PER"],["Earl Gast","PER"],["Energy","ORG"],["David Goldwyn","PER"],["Department of Energy","ORG"],["Department of Homeland Security","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["Justine Lindemann","PER"],["Justine","PER"],["Lindemann","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 11, 2009","entities":[["APEC","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Singapore","LOC"],["Obama Administration","ORG"],["Asia","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["APEC","ORG"],["Singapore","LOC"],["Yoh","PER"],["Lim","PER"],["APEC","ORG"],["North Korea","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["North Korea","LOC"],["Stephen Bosworth","PER"],["Pyongyang","LOC"],["Six Party","MISC"],["Bosworth","PER"],["Korean Peninsula","LOC"],["Six Party Talk","MISC"],["North Koreans","MISC"],["North Korea","LOC"],["Six Party","MISC"],["Six Party","MISC"],["Korean","MISC"],["Peninsula","LOC"],["United","LOC"],["States","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"],["Burmese","MISC"],["Burma","LOC"],["##EA","ORG"],["Burmese","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 11, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"],["Azerbaijani","MISC"],["Emin Milli","PER"],["Adnan Hajizade","PER"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Azerbaijan","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["Joe Yun","PER"],["Southeast Asia","LOC"],["Susan Reichle","PER"],["USAID","ORG"],["Alan Dwyer","PER"],["USAID","ORG"],["East Asia Pacific","LOC"],["Rick Scott","PER"],["USAID","ORG"],["East Asia","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Joe","PER"],["Mark","PER"],["USAID","ORG"],["Manila","LOC"],["Asia","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Singapore","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Singapore","LOC"],["Singapore","LOC"],["APEC","ORG"],["Manila","LOC"],["Singapore","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["APEC","ORG"],["Manila","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Powell","PER"],["Manila","LOC"],["East Asia","LOC"],["Japan South Korea Thailand","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["Asian","MISC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["R","ORG"],["Arroyo","PER"],["Manila","LOC"],["Philippines","LOC"],["##EA","ORG"],["Filipino","MISC"],["Southeast Asia","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["International Narcotics and Law Enforcement Affairs","ORG"],["David T","PER"],["Johnson","PER"],["Organization of American States OAS","ORG"],["Inter American Drug Abuse Control Commission","ORG"],["Jose Miguel Insulza","PER"],["OAS","ORG"],["David Johnson","PER"],["Bureau for International Narcotics and Law Enforcement Affairs","ORG"],["A","PER"],["Tom McLellan","PER"],["Office of National Drug Control Policy","ORG"],["Round Table","MISC"],["San Martin Room","LOC"],["Miami Florida","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["CICAD","ORG"],["CICAD","ORG"],["17th Street","LOC"],["Constitution Avenue N","LOC"],["W","LOC"],["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["OAS Press Department","ORG"],["Pablo Ros","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["Zimbabwe","LOC"],["Kimberley Process","MISC"],["K","MISC"],["Swakopmund Namibia","LOC"],["Zimbabwe","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Work Plan","MISC"],["Zimbabwe","LOC"],["KP","ORG"],["Zimbabwe","LOC"],["K","MISC"],["Zimbabwe","LOC"],["Marange","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["Zimbabwe","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Guinea","LOC"],["K","MISC"],["##P","ORG"],["K","MISC"],["##P","ORG"],["Kimberley","MISC"],["Process","ORG"],["K","MISC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["Arturo Valenzuela","PER"],["Patrick Kennedy","PER"],["Valenzuela","PER"],["Center for Latin American Studies","ORG"],["Edmund A","ORG"],["Walsh","ORG"],["School","LOC"],["of Foreign Service","ORG"],["Georgetown University","ORG"],["Latin American","MISC"],["U","MISC"],["S.","MISC"],["Latin American","MISC"],["Georgetown","ORG"],["Council on Latin American Studies","ORG"],["Duke University","ORG"],["Oxford University","ORG"],["University of Sussex","ORG"],["University of Florence","ORG"],["Italy","LOC"],["Catholic University of","ORG"],["Chile","LOC"],["Clinton","PER"],["Valenzuela","PER"],["White House","LOC"],["Inter American","MISC"],["National Security Council","ORG"],["Inter American","MISC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Department of State","ORG"],["United States","LOC"],["Mexico","LOC"],["Council on Foreign Relations","ORG"],["##eric","LOC"],["American Higher Education","ORG"],["National Order of the Southern Cross","MISC"],["Brazil","LOC"],["Order of Boyaca","MISC"],["Colombia","LOC"],["Valenzuela","PER"],["Drew University","ORG"],["National Democratic Institute for International Affairs NDI","ORG"],["National Council of La Raza NCLR","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["Institut des Ameriques","ORG"],["Paris","LOC"],["Science","MISC"],["Columbia University","ORG"],["A","MISC"],["Science","MISC"],["Religion","MISC"],["Drew University","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["Raj Shah","PER"],["United States Agency for International Development","ORG"],["Obama","PER"],["American","MISC"],["Africa","LOC"],["Asia","LOC"],["Global Alliance for V","ORG"],["##ac","MISC"],["##cines and Immunization","ORG"],["Global Fund","ORG"],["aids TB","MISC"],["Malaria","MISC"],["Africa","LOC"],["Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation","ORG"],["Research Education and Economics","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S. Department of Agriculture","ORG"],["Raj","PER"],["Congress","ORG"],["State Department","ORG"],["White House","ORG"],["USAID","ORG"],["Alonzo L. Ful","PER"],["##am","PER"],["USA","LOC"],["##ID","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["Lincoln Center","LOC"],["The Rhythm Road American Music A","MISC"],["##ad","MISC"],["United States","LOC"],["New York City","LOC"],["American","MISC"],["Americans","MISC"],["Maura M. Pally","PER"],["and Cultural","ORG"],["America","LOC"],["Dizzy Gillespie Louis Armstrong","PER"],["Dave Brubeck","PER"],["Rhythm Road","ORG"],["National Geographic Society","ORG"],["Grosvenor Auditorium","LOC"],["Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Club Coca Cola","ORG"],["Frederick P. Rose Hall","LOC"],["Lincoln Center","LOC"],["Rhythm Road","MISC"],["Student Loan","ORG"],["Johnny Rodgers","PER"],["Mark Sherman Tim Horne","PER"],["##r Quartet Jazz New","ORG"],["Jersey","LOC"],["Nasar Abadey","PER"],["Supernova Jazz Fusion","ORG"],["Joe","PER"],["McLerran Quartet","ORG"],["Oscar Williams","PER"],["##se Gospel","ORG"],["Chen Lo","PER"],["Liberation Family","ORG"],["Hop","ORG"],["Charlie Porter Quartet","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["United States","LOC"],["Australia Canada Germany","LOC"],["Netherlands","LOC"],["United Kingdom","LOC"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["United States Civilian Response Corps","ORG"],["Reconstruction and Stabilization","ORG"],["Canada","LOC"],["Stabilization and Reconstruction Task Force","ORG"],["United Kingdom","LOC"],["SU","ORG"],["Office of the Australian Civilian Corps","ORG"],["Germany","LOC"],["Division","ORG"],["Foreign Office","ORG"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Netherlands","LOC"],["Building","ORG"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 10, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S.","MISC"],["Ecuadorian","MISC"],["s","MISC"],["Washington DC","LOC"],["United States","LOC"],["Ecuador","LOC"],["Office of the United States Trade Representative","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S.","MISC"],["- Ecuador Trade and Investment Council","ORG"],["Ecuadorian","MISC"],["Jorge Orbe","PER"],["Western Hemisphere","LOC"],["Thomas Shannon","PER"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Quito Ecuador","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 9, 2009","entities":[["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["Yoani Sanchez Orlando Luis Pardo","PER"],["Claudia Cadelo","PER"],["Havana","LOC"],["World Freedom Day","MISC"],["World Freedom Day","MISC"],["Cuba","LOC"],["Cuban","MISC"],["Yoani Sanchez Orlando Luis Pardo","PER"],["Claudia Cadelo","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 9, 2009","entities":[["Industry Advisory Panel","ORG"],["Bureau of Overseas Buildings Operations","ORG"],["U","ORG"],["S","ORG"],["Department of State","ORG"],["C Street","LOC"],["23rd Street Washington D","LOC"],["C","LOC"],["Bureau","ORG"],["Bureau of Overseas Buildings Operations","ORG"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["U","LOC"],["S","LOC"],["23rd","LOC"],["Jonathan Blyth","PER"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 9, 2009","entities":[["Arkansas","LOC"],["Arkansas","LOC"],["Bill","PER"],["Cold War","MISC"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Kennedy","PER"],["Tom Brokaw","PER"],["Berlin","LOC"],["Soviet Union","LOC"],["Eastern","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Bill","PER"],["Helmut Kohl","PER"],["Germany","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Eastern","MISC"],["Europe","LOC"],["EU","ORG"],["NATO","ORG"],["Europe","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Soviet","MISC"],["Union","LOC"]]}
{"publish_date":"November 9, 2009","entities":[["Berlin","LOC"],["Arkansas","LOC"],["Tom Brokaw","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Tom Brokaw","PER"],["Cold War","MISC"],["Germany","LOC"],["German","MISC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["German","MISC"],["East","LOC"],["West","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Merkel","PER"],["United States","LOC"],["Congress","ORG"],["Germany","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Afghanistan","LOC"],["Iran","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Obama","PER"],["Obama","PER"],["Germany","LOC"],["German","MISC"],["Europe","LOC"],["Germany","LOC"]]}
